1937年  美利坚共和国
-几点开始的  -5点整  已经开始7分钟了
-When did it start? -At 05:00. We're seven minutes in.
列兵米勒
Private Miller
你已吸入9号试剂达7分13秒
You've been smoking ltem 9 for seven minutes and 13 seconds.
我们要问你几个问题
We're going to ask you several questions.
现在感觉如何
How do you feel?
长官
Well, sir
我觉得像
I feel like a
像是一片黄油
Like a slice of butter
融化在一堆又大又硬的烙饼上
melting on top of a big old pile of flapjacks.
就这样
Yeah.
好  列兵米勒  当你想到你的上司
Okay, Private Miller, when you think of your superiors
情绪如何
What emotions do you feel?
列兵米勒
Okay, private Miller?
这正常吗
Is this normal?
列兵
Okay, private
列兵米勒
Okay, private Miller?
Private Miller.
回答问题
Answer the question.
熄了  长官
This went out, sir.
借个火
Can you torch me?
我们会派人进去
We'll send someone in.
老天爷啊
Holy bejesus!
列兵米勒  回答问题
Private Miller, answer the question.
再问一遍  长官
What was the question again, sir?
当你想到你的上司  情绪如何
When you think of your superiors, what emotions do you feel?
你知道我为什么跟
You know what problem I have
那个人模狗样的叫做军队的玩意儿对着干吗
with your fucking little dog-and-pony act you call the military?
这么说吧  第一  一群傻冒
Here it is. One, lots of dudes.
傻冒去哪里了
Where are the boobies?
第二  我们跑这地底下干吗来着  长官
Two, why are we underground right now, sir?
为什么不在光天化日之下  为什么不在操场上
Why can't we be out in the open? why aren't we in a square right now?
为什么不能告诉人们  让他们知道9号试剂的存在
Why aren't we talking to people, letting them know ltem 9 exists?
敲锣打鼓的告诉他们
Get it out, shout the roof tops
绝无仅有  9号试剂真是棒极了
"this is great! this is the bee's knees"ltem 9!"
列兵  请正经点
Private, we need you to be serious.
我正经的很  你的小弟弟  我的嘴
I'm serious. Your dick, my mouth.
真丢人
That's inappropriate.
操你
Fuck you!
我看够了  终止吧
I've seen enough. Shut it down.
掩埋实验舱  卖掉这块地  把他也处理了
Bury the hatch, sell the land, and dispose of him.
此事从未发生过
This never happened.
哥们儿  你眼睛咋了
Dude, what happened to your eye?
喂
Hello.
听不懂我说啥吗
Can you guys understand me?
-喂喂  我们去哪里  -我是布拉特将军
-Hey. hey, where we going? -This is general Brat.
我们对9号试剂已得出最终结论
We've reached a final conclusion on ltem 9.
非法
Illegal!
我是山姆  早安
Hey, this is Sam. good morning.
欢迎收听公路之声
Welcome to KRAD.
我认为上一位连线听众的部分观点不可否认
You know, I think that last caller had some undeniable points.
现在来接听下一位打进电话的朋友  戴尔·丹顿
Right now, we're gonna get to the next caller, Dale Denton.
山姆,我是忠实粉丝  第一次打进来
Hey, Sam. Big huge fan. First-time caller.
-我这么认为  -说吧
-Here's my piece. -all right.
如果大麻在未来5年内被禁
If marijuana is not legal within the next five years
我对人类就彻底失去信心了
I have no faith left in humanity, period.
人人都爱抽那玩意儿
Everyone likes smoking weed.
都延续几千年了  不可能说禁就禁
They have for thousands of years. They're not gonna stop anytime soon.
它让生活充满阳光  吃的也好吃了  音乐也更棒了
It makes everything better, makes food better, makes music better.
做爱也更爽了  感谢上帝
It makes sex feel better, for god's sakes.
就连狗屎电影都好看了  懂吧
It makes shitty movies better, you know?
你好  是桑德拉·黛比吗
Hi, there. Are you Sandra Danby?
没错
Yeah.
我是格尔茨  来自全球救助中心  这是
Well, I'm garth from global saviors, and
-这是什么  -开个玩笑
-What is this? -I'm joking.
4次离婚仲裁你都没出席
You failed to show up for divorce proceedings
根据法院指令  你被传召了
four times under court order, and you've been served.
-好极了  谢了混蛋  -抱歉
-Oh, great. Thanks a lot, asshole. -Sorry.
爱没有年龄界限
I'm just saying love has no age.
你不要一直跟我说  由于你的年龄
You can't instantly tell me that a man, because he's a certain age
你不能和女人相爱  更不能结婚
can't marry a woman or love a woman.
我正在和一个高中女生约会呢
I'm dating a high-school girl.
你还没发掘出潜力吧
You're not maximizing your potential.
你觉得那妞是来真格的吗
Do you want to think this girl takes you seriously?
不  但是如果我25而那姑娘18的话
No, but if I'm 25 and the girl is 18 years old
也许世俗眼光看来  有点糟糕  但是
you know, in society, that might look bad. But
-还得两情相悦呢  -我认为事实如此
-Hey! As long as it's consensual. -I think it's consensual.
你  你被传召了
Yo, you been served.
你被传召了  你被传召了
You've been served. You've been served.
你被传召了
You've been served.
沃尔特·瓦达斯卡三世
Walter Wadska the third.
你是来修传真机的吧
You here to fix the fax machine?
不  我来通知你  你的信用卡欠账4068美元
No, I'm here to tell you you owe mastercard 4068 bucks.
你被传召了  乐意效劳
You've been served by the best. Keep it real.
你就不能找个正经活儿  你这烂人
Why don't you get a real job, you fucking cocksucker?
-"霓虹大街"  -没错
-Hey, "electric avenue." -I know, right?
-能打到下一关吗  -行  我会的
-Take that shit to the next level, eh? -Okay, I will.
-埃德加·特伦斯医生?  -是我
-Dr. Edgar Terrence? -yes.
由于你多次拒绝修剪猴面包树
You have repeatedly refused to trim the monkey tree
至使其枝干已侵入邻居的房产
that spills onto your neighbor's property.
鉴于此事  你被传召了
And now because of that, you've been served.
你这混球
You're a jerk.
现在的系统
All this current system is doing
就是在把钱往罪犯手里塞
is putting money in the hands of criminals
致使你我这样的平凡人物和罪犯抗争
And it's making ordinary people like you and me deal with those criminals.
你和毒贩打过交道吗
You ever dealt with a drug dealer?
真是可怕  怪异又棘手
It's terrible, it's weird, it's awkward.
他们以为他们是你的朋友  其实不是
They think they're your friend, but they're not.
戴尔我懂了  谢谢你的来电  下一位听众  谢谢
Dale, I get your point. Thanks for your input. Next caller, please.
我不能去了
I can't come.
什么
What?
你他妈说啥  戴尔
Why the fuck not, Dale?
我只是  听着  我不能去了
I just Look, I can't come.
明天我有一堆事  手忙脚乱
I have a lot of stuff to do tomorrow. It's a bad day for me.
见鬼  戴尔  你怎么不早说
Jesus christ, Dale. When were you gonna tell me?
我妈准备了整整一天
My mom has been shopping all day.
-干吗这么急  -她都已准备了蒸粗麦粉
-Why she's been shopping all day? -She's already planning on couscous.
我说我可能会去  她就迫不及待去准备
I said I might be able to go. So why is she doing that already?
-现在我里外不是人  -你就是个混蛋
-Now I look like an asshole. -You are one.
宝贝儿  别这么说  我只是去不成了  我要干活
Come on, don't say that. I just can't go. I have a job.
-行吧  -"行"?
-Fine. -"fine"?
别来了  我不在乎了
Don't come. I don't care.
你不在乎  那为什么邀请我  我以为你想我去呢
You don't care? Then why have you been inviting me? I thought you wanted me to go.
如果你不想见他们  我也懒得招呼你
Because if you don't wanna meet them, I don't want you to.
我想去  但有工作  去不了  对不起  你还想我怎么办
I want to. I can't. I have a job. I'm sorry. what do you want from me?
我知道他们会喜欢你的  如此而已
I just know they'll like you. That's all.
你人很好  也很风趣
You're great, and you're funny
很性感
and you're sexy.
我想让他们知道
I just want them to see that.
-你想让他们知道我很性感  -二位
-You want them to see that I'm sexy? -Hey, people?
-爱德华先生  -需要效劳吗
-Hi, Mr. Edwards. -Can I help you?
不  没事  谢了
No, I'm good. Thank you, though.
是吗  我看见你没带访客牌  才有此一问
Yeah? I see you don't have a visitor's badge. That's why I ask.
-我是和她一起的  -其实  这是我的男朋友
-I'm with her, actually. -Actually, this is my boyfriend.
我听到了  但愿听错了
I heard that. I wish I didn't hear that, but I just heard that.
你啥意思啊
What's that supposed to mean?
你怎么不找个同龄女朋友呢
I'm just wondering why you don't date a nice guy your own age.
-就她年龄而言  她很成熟  -对
-She's very mature for her age. -Yeah.
-安吉  你好啊  -你好
-Angie, hey. how's it going? -Hey.
克拉克  你好  怎么了
Hey, Clark, how you doing, man? What's up?
没事  哥们  我挺好
I'm good, bro. I'm good.
伙计  我想告诉你
Dude, I wanted to tell you.
今天的戏剧课上你可真是惟妙惟肖
You were hilarious today in drama class.
说真的你演的杰夫·高布伦笑得我差点尿裤子
Seriously your Jeff Goldblum impression made me pee my pants.
真的
I wish.
差点忘了
Oh, hey, I almost forgot.
上周我们外出演出时  你把短裤落在我车里了
Last week when we worked out, you forgot your shorts in my car.
对
Oh, yeah.
-给你  -谢了
-Here you go. -Thanks.
小意思  小意思
Yeah, no problem, no problem.
-帮我拿下  -好的
-Can you hold those? -Yeah.
演出如何啊  壮哥
How's it going, sporty spice?
他是我男朋友  戴尔
This is my boyfriend, dale.
-幸会幸会  -彼此彼此
-Hey, nice to meet you. -You too.
我可是久仰大名  听说你酷毙了
I've heard so much about you. You're real cool.
-我是说  你很棒  -对  棒极了
-I mean, you're great. Yeah. -yeah, awesome.
等明年  明年哥们儿  大学了  大学啊
Anyways, yeah, dude, next year. Next year college, man. College.
一定爽歪歪  我会替你照顾她的
Gonna be kick-ass. I will watch her back for you.
我知道那儿成群结队的小子等着勾搭她呢
I know there's tons of guys that are gonna be trying to get on that shit.
-好  -因为我知道  好
-oh, good. -Because I got that yeah.
你也要照看她  好极了
You got her ass? Perfect.
-我会照看她是为了  -他是好意
-I'll watch her ass for -He's trying to be nice.
-家政课见  -好
-I'll catch you at home ec. -Okay.
你们还一起上家政课  不错啊
You guys got home ec together too. That's cool.
-我们有好几门课一起  -幸会
-We got a few classes together. -Nice to meet you.
青春苦短  要及时行乐啊
Time to suck today's dick. That's what I'm talking about.
回见
See you guys later.
-回见  克拉克  -克拉克是个好小伙子
-all right, Clark. -Clark's a great guy.
他会好好照顾安吉拉的  哥们儿
He's totally gonna take care of Angela, man.
他不错  是个做实验的好搭档
He's great. He's a wonderful lab partner.
那太棒了  他会照顾好她的
So that's gonna be cool.He'll keep an eye on her.
你怎么还不滚  你这个怪鸟
Why don't you go fuck yourself, you weird prick?
我是老师  你不能这么和我说话
I'm a teacher. You can't talk to me like that.
我不是学生  所以我想说啥就说啥
I'm not a student, so I can say whatever I want
-你这个毛都没长齐的类人猿  -其实
-You chimp-fucking little bastard. -Actually
限你1分30秒内离开学校范围
You've got t-minus 30 seconds to get off school property
不然我就叫保安
or I call the liaison officer.
-我们这就走  抱歉  -竖中指也不能让我掐停表
-We're leaving. I'm sorry. -Middle finger won't stop the clock.
什么玩意儿啊
What a jerk.
那家伙有病啊  见鬼
What's that guy's problem? Jesus.
我不知道  通常他  是很奇怪
I don't normally he's that's really weird.
明晚我非常乐意和你全家共进晚餐
You know what? I'd love to have dinner with you and your parents tomorrow night.
我要走了  真的得走了  我得重新安排事情
I'm gonna go. I'll definitely go. I'll shuffle things around
-真的?  -真的  我一定到
-Really? -Yeah, I'll be there for sure.
我想让他们知道  你找了个好对象
Yeah, I wanna show them you're in good hands. yeah.
我没什么可扭扭捏捏的
I got nothing to be embarrassed about.
这对我和家里人都太有意义了
That means so much to me and my parents.
没问题  一切都会十分完美的
No problem. it's gonna be awesome.
-喂  -索尔  方便我过去吗
-Hello? -Hey, Saul. mind if I come by?
-来吧  -好  就到
-come on down. -sweet. be there.
玛丽
Hi, mary
我以为飓风季节已经过去了呢
I thought the hurricane season was over.
I thought hurricane season was over.
我很遗憾  事情失控了
I'm sorry. Things just got out of hand.
没错  我的第一任丈夫也说这话来着
Yeah, that's the way it was with my first husband.
-有人吗  -老兄
-Hello? -Hey, man.
我操  老兄
What the fuck, man?
我没给你开门啊  你丫的怎么钻进来的
I didn't buzz you in. How the monkey did you get in here?
有个遛鸟的给我开了门  他正好出去
Some guy with a fauxhawk let me in. He was leaving when l
-狗日的凯尔  -也许是凯尔吧
-Fucking Kyle. -It might have been kyle.
-狗日的  -抱歉  老兄
-Asshole. -I'm sorry, man.
门铃要了有个屁用
What the fuck's the buzzer for anyway?
我不知道  对不起  我不知道你们的规矩
I don't know. I'm sorry about that. I don't know your protocol yet.
省省吧  不是你的错
Stuff your sorries in a sack. it's not your fault.
-好的  -都是这群狗日的  坐吧
-Okay. -It's these jerk-offs. have a seat.
好  谢了  谢谢
Okay, cool. thanks, man. awesome.
来  看这个
Yo, check this out.
卫星广播
Satellite radio.
有2台电视又有收音机  酷毙了
Got two tvs and radio. that's pretty rad.
居家必备啊
That's home entertainment.
你可真会享受  哇  还有张可爱的相片
You're very entertained. Oh, wow. You got a cute picture too.
没错 我和我奶奶
Oh, yeah. me and my bubbe.
我问问
Hey, let me ask you something.
什么
Yeah?
如有必要  你会亲手终结某人吗
Do you think you could pull the plug on someone if you needed to?
比如安乐死
Like, euthanasia?
比方说  对她?
Like, on her?
如果必须如此
If I needed to.
我有点急事  老兄
I'm kind of in a hurry, man.
我不知道就这话题是不是该继续往下聊
I don't know if we should start going down that road.
我能跟你探讨一整天的安乐死  还是算了吧
I could talk all day about euthanasia. don't get me started.
-也许我们可以  -下次吧
-Maybe we should -We'll save it.
-下次再聊这个  -信你一次
-Save it for next time. -I'll take that rain check.
生意归生意
Business for the businessman.
-对  你有我的号  -对
-Yeah, you got my number. -okay.
-来点实际的  -好
-Brass tacks. -Yes.
我刚搞到一批简直就是我抽过的极品中的极品
I just got a shipment of the dopest dope I've ever smoked.
绝对是极品中的极品
Hands down, dopest dope I've ever smoked.
不可能比印度神油更爽  不可能  我不信
Not better than the blue oyster. It can't be. I can't handle that.
这就跟印度神油与阿富汗土烟碰上
This is like if that blue oyster shit met that afghan kush I had
结婚生个崽儿
and they had a baby.
然后  我那种疯狂北极光
And meanwhile, that crazy northern lights stuff I had
和超级红色雪花混合  再生个崽儿
and the super red especial snowflake met and had a baby.
俩杂种神奇的操在一起
And by some miracle, those two babies met and fucked
然后就生下这玩意儿
this would be the shit that they birthed.
-真的  -这玩意儿就是个杂种
-yes. -this is the product of baby fucking.
-闻闻  -好
-smell it. -okay.
闻闻  慢慢闻
Smell it. enjoy.
就跟上帝的私处一样
It's like god's vagina.
怎么样  想不想徜徉其中
What, you wanna bathe in it?
-我想生生世世跟它过  -要不要?
-I wanna live in here. -you wanna be it?
上帝啊  我要把它塞进我的鼻子里  闻个够
My god, I just wanna shove it up my nose, have that smell all day.
-太神了  -随你往哪儿塞
-That's amazing. -Shove it anywhere you like.
太美妙了  这叫什么
Beautiful. what's it called?
-菠萝快车  -菠萝快车
-Pineapple express. -Pineapple express.
就像厄尔尼诺现象一样
It's this thing, like, el nino
从夏威夷和加拿大席卷而来
This airflow that comes from hawaii and canada.
用特殊的手段  完美的混合了烟土和大麻
It gets the dirt, mixes it in with the weed in a special way.
技术含量很高  现在我都没捣鼓清楚
It's very scientific. I won't go into it right now.
不过这整座城里就我有货
But I am the only guy in the whole city that has it.
四分之一磅  只加10块
Only 10 bones more for a quarter.
好  来一份
Okay, I'll take a quarter.
-好  成交  -谢了
-all right, you're on. -thank you very much.
我去拿秤
Let me get my scale.
去吧  拿秤吧  让我赶紧带走
Get it going. grab the scale. let's get me out of here.
我以为飓风季节已经过了
I thought hurricane season was over.
这是啥  狗日的
Where are you, you little fucker?
这他妈的什么玩意儿
What the fuck is this thing?
-十字嗦  -是吗
-cross joint. -yeah.
-没尝过吧  -这玩意能抽
-you ever smoke one of those? -you can smoke this?
-对啊  老兄  -不
-yeah, man. -no.
这就是未来
This is the future.
就像工程连接里顶点和旋转件的结合
This is, like, the apex of the vortex of joint engineering.
据说第一支是欧·肖内西发明的
It's rumored that m. m. O'Shaughnessy designed the first one.
就是设计金门大桥的那家伙
The guy who designed the Golden Gate Bridge.
是我第二崇拜的建筑工程师了
My second favorite civil engineer
仅次于设计麦迪逊花园广场的汉斯卡尔·班德尔
behind Hannskarl Bandel, Madison Square Garden.
你要同时点燃三个头
What you do is you light all three ends at the same time.
-真的  -然后等烟雾聚集
-Really? -And then the smoke converges
混成一种三重混合粉末
creating a trifecta of joint-smoking power.
就是这个  老兄  这是你孙子辈才能抽上的
This is it, man. This is what your grandchildren are gonna be smoking.
未来  这是未来
Future. the future.
太神了  称好了
That's amazing. well, got the weed?
-对  -装袋打包  美妙啊  好了
-yeah. -in the bag. beautiful. okay.
小心点  老兄  一手交钱  一手交货
Be careful with that thing, man. here's the cash, grab the stash.
好了  老兄  谢了  继续享受吧
Alrighty, man, thanks. have a good one.
别伤了自己  再见
Don't hurt yourself. adios.
等等  老兄
Well, hey, wait a minute, man.
咱们把这玩意儿抽了吧
Let's smoke this fucking thing.
我真的  不行  老兄  我得
I really I can't, man. I gotta
我自己点都点不着
I can't even light this thing on my own.
老兄  你需要帮手
I need your help, man.
-好吧我来  -来吧
-I'm in. -Come on!
-说干就干  -快坐
-Why not? let's do it. -Come on down!
为啥不呢  该怎么做
Why not? What do I do?
好  听着
Okay, here's what you do.
-先拿好  -我来拿
-You equip yourself. -I'm equipping.
-我拿好了  长官  -好了
-Equip me, sir. -Okay.
当我点这头  你要把这两头给点着
You are going to light these two ends while I light this end.
-行  -准备好了吗
-Okay. -Are you ready?
-好了  -点火升空
-Ready. -Blast off.
-我来一口  -好  来吧
-I'm gonna do it. -Good. Go for it.
咳出来会比较好受
It's better to cough.
就像
It's like
比大麻和菠萝快车混吸
Makes you 10 times more higher
还要爽上10倍
than the cross weed and the pineapple express.
老兄  你他妈就跟要升天了似的
You're like, totally fucking gong show'ed, man.
操
Oh, fuck.
等一下  老兄
Hang on one second, man.
你个狗娘养的
Oh, you fucker.
谁呀
Who is it?
是克里斯·吉博尔特  开门  老兄
It's Chris Gebert, man. let me up.
妈的
Shit.
是吉博尔特呀?
What's a Gebert?
上来吧
Come on up.
他一根菠萝快车也甭想拿到
He ain't getting any of that pineapple express.
他来拿大麻的
Chris is getting snicklefritz.
听着  老兄
So listen, man.
我得问问  那
I gotta ask you. so
听着  老兄  你在我这儿买东西2个月了吧
Listen, man. you've been buying from me for, like, two months, right?
-两个月  -我得问问  老兄
-two months. -I gotta ask, man.
你这身衣服是干吗的
What's up with the suit?
我是司法服务传达员  我必须穿这套
I'm a process server. so I have to wear a suit.
公务员  就跟管家似的?
Wow, you're a servant? like a butler?
-司机?  -不  不  什么?  不是  我不是
-A chauffeur? -No. no. what? no, I'm not
-擦鞋的?  -我是传达员
-Shine shoes? -I'm a process server.
-就像  -处理垃圾的
-I like -in process.
我给一个公司干
I work for a company that's, like, hired
就像被律师雇佣  发送法律文件等
by lawyers to hand out legal documents.
就像给那些不想收件的人发传票那样
Like subpoenas to people who don't want them.
有时候得改头换面
I gotta wear disguises sometimes just
来让他们承认自己的身份
To make them admit they're themselves
这样才能把文件送到他们手里
so I can serve them the papers.
改头换面
Disguise.
类似  我想
Kind of, I guess.
-是个混蛋活儿  -很酷啊  老兄
-it's a hell of a job. -that's cool, man.
-日复一日  一般般吧  比如今天我坐在车里
Like a day-to-day basis, it's fine. like today, i, like, sat in my car
我抽了大概  10根吧
i smoked, like, 10 doobies
然后就去找我的女朋友吃午餐
and then I went to go visit my girlfriend at lunch.
不错啊
Nice.
什么  你舔她咪咪了
What? you sucked on her titties?
不  就亲嘴而已  耍酷罢了
No, I just kissed her. I just did that to make it seem cool.
酷毙了  她也好这一口
That's cool. Does she like to smoke weed?
偶尔吧  她有几个
A little sometimes. she has a couple
她在上高中  所以和许多高中生一样
She's in high school, so as much as any high-school kid.
真是一酷到底
She's cool as hell, actually.
-你会喜欢她的  -真的?
-You'd get along with her. -Really?
是的  比较烂的就是
Yeah, you know, it only sucks
我去高中学校看她时  跟她一起上学的男生
When I go visit her in high school and the guys she goes to school with
高大威猛又风趣
are strong and handsome and really funny.
就像杰夫·高布伦那么耀眼,真操蛋
Like, do good impressions of jeff goldblum and shit like that.
我就像个蠢猪
And, like, I just feel like a fat, dumb
我在那真是一无是处
Fucking stinky ass-turd when I'm there.
-什么  -真是  真是丢人
-what? -it really it sucks for my ego.
-杰夫·高布伦是个杂种  -这是我说的
-Fuck jeff goldblum, man. -That's what I say.
别不自信  你有个好女孩
You know, don't get down on yourself. you got a great girl.
不错的工作  无忧无虑
You got a great job where you don't do anything.
还能成天抽大烟
You get to smoke weed all day.
我求之不得
I wish I had that.
开什么玩笑?  你拥有全球最轻松的工作
Are you kidd? you do. you have the easiest job on earth.
-你也每天都能抽  -没错
-you do smoke weed all day. -that's true.
别忘了
You didn't think of that.
-我是有个好工作  -是啊  你什么都不用做
-I do have a good job. -yeah, you do nothing.
-谢谢  哥们儿  -不用
-Thanks, man. -No prob.
谢谢
Thank you.
奶奶的  好了  先做生意
Oh, shit. all right. business.
-衣袋还整齐吧  -还好
-got my persona. -yeah, yeah.
把那十字嗦灭了
Hey. put that cross joint out.
他看到的话  就不想走了
He sees that, he'll never get the fuck out of here.
-克里斯  怎么样啊  -索尔
-what's up, chris? -yo, hey, Saul.
混的咋样啊  哥们
how you doing, buddy?
不错  挺好
All right, homes. good.
-他是谁  -我朋友马克
-who's this? -hey. oh, that's my friend Mark.
一手交钱  一手交货
You got the dough? there you go.
-谢谢  -很好  马克  很高兴认识你
-appreciate it. -nice. good to meet you, Mark.
-请问有镇静剂吗  -镇静剂?
-do you have any percocet, please? -percocet?
你说什么  我不卖那种垃圾
What are you talking about? I don't sell that shit.
克里斯
Chris
克里斯  你跟他说我卖那玩意
Chirs you told him I was gonna sell percocet?
-我没说你卖镇静剂  -那是怎么回事
-I didn't say anything about percocet. -what the fuck?
-我只想要点镇静剂  -那个  我
-I just wanted a couple percocets. -well, i
你来错地方了  来错了
You came to the wrong place. wrong place.
-抱歉  -没事  当心点  哥们儿
-Sorry. -yeah, nice. Peace out, homes.
-感谢  -上帝
-Thank -god.
-什么玩意嘛  -嗯
-what the fuck? -yeah.
-该死的蠢货  -是啊
-fucking lingerer. -yeah, totally.
-蠢货  -难对付
-lingerer. -hardcore.
妈的
Fuck.
-烦死我了  -也烦死我了
-bums me out. -bums me out too.
要是让我碰到讨厌的人  真想死了算了
If there's one quality I hate in a person, it's lingering.
-没错  我们都一样  -没错
-That's right. you and me both. -yeah, yeah.
我很好奇  你效力工作服务的那些人
So I'm curious. what have those people done that you go
都干了什么
and process and service?
我也不知道  我猜是不同寻常的事
I don't know. it's always something different, I guess.
这个人
This guy
泰德·琼斯  谁知道呢  你认识吗
Ted Jones, who knows. you know?
-泰德·琼斯?  -认识吗
-Ted Jones? -yeah, why?
我兄弟瑞得从他那买货  他在泰德·琼斯那拿货
My guy, Red, who I buy from, he gets his stuff from a Ted Jones.
-是吗  -可能是同一个人
-Really? -Maybe it's the same guy.
真奇怪
That'd be weird.
我觉得这名字很普通  可是
It's a pretty normal name, I guess, but
无论如何  我真的得走了  我走了
Anyway, I should really get going, man. I gotta go.
干活  见到你很开心  谢谢
Duty calls, but it's good to see you. thanks.
你刚抽完就走?  待会儿
You're gonna smoke and run? come on, man.
我们可以一起在网上看些疯狂的东西
We can go look at some crazy things on the internet together.
听起来不错  但是  我想说
That sounds appealing, but you know what? I'll tell here
过几天我就抽完了  到时再来一起玩
I'm gonna run out of weed in a couple days. I'll come by, hang out.
-我们看227之类的  -再好不过了
-We'll watch 227 and shit. -definitely.
酷  谢谢  很高兴见到你
Cool, man. well, thanks. good to see you.
-当心  哥们儿  -好的
-Peace, brother. -okay.
想你
One love.
你什么时候也抵押
When you got behind on the mortgage
有人贷款给你了吗
someone finally made you a loan?
是的  贷了
Yes, he did.
贷了  利息多少
Yes, he did. what was the interest rate you got?
-12%或13%  -真恶心
-It was 12 or 13 percent. -That's disgusting.
-喂?  -喂
-hello? -hello.
安吉  怎么样?
Hey, Angie, what's happening?
我刚跟我妈谈过  你能来吃晚饭他们很高兴
I just talked to my mom, and they are so excited you're coming for dinner.
非常高兴  我也是  我们真的都非常高兴
Like, so excited. and so am i, but we're all really excited.
谢谢
Thank you so much.
没什么  我有心理准备  会很好的
No problem. I'm psyched too. it's gonna be awesome.
蒸粗麦粉  这东西好吃  听着就留口水
Couscous. the food so nice, they named it twice.
戴尔  不管怎么样  我迫不及待想要结束这该死的高中生活
Dale, anyway, I can't wait for next year when this bullshit's over.
妈的  客户来了  等会儿打给你
Oh, shit. I see the guy I gotta serve. I'll call you back.
死警察  妈的
Fucking cops. shit.
上帝
Jesus.
多么可爱的小警察啊
What an adorable little cop.
好奇怪
Weird.
上帝  妈呀
Jesus. fuck.
那是什么
What the fuck was that?
妈的
Oh, shit.
伙计  伙计
Dude. dude. dude. dude.
不
Oh, no!
-快开  开  -那是谁
-Drive, Drive. -Who the fuck is that?
我不知道  但一定要抓住他
I don't know, but I ain't waiting to see.
菠萝快车
Pineapple express.
天哪  天哪
Oh, my god! oh, my god! oh, my god! oh, my god!
我看到脑浆还有血
I saw brains and blood!
快  快跑
Come on! come on!
我该去哪里
Where do I go?
谁啊
Hello?
索尔  我是戴尔  让我进去  让我进去
Saul, it's dale. let me in. let me in.
我看到很疯狂的事  快开门
I just saw some crazy shit. please. let me in.
-我是戴尔·丹顿  让我进去  -戴尔?
-it's dale denton. let me in, man. -dale?
是  戴尔  早说过了  让我进去
Yes, dale. that's what I said. it's dale. let me in.
好的  上来吧
Oh, all right, man. come on up.
我开了  我按的时候你开门
I buzzed it. open the door when I buzz it.
精确到3秒钟
Buzz it in three seconds exactly.
1  2
One, two
-行了吗  -第3秒再开
-Did it work? -on three!
我是第3秒开的  1  2  3  开
I did it on three. on "one, two, three, go"?
就是第3秒
Just on three.
-那个狗娘养的杀了他  -别吵到邻居
-He fucking killed him. -hey, I got neighbors.
那个狗娘养的杀了他
He fucking killed him.
-谁杀了谁  -一个女警还有一个男的
-Who killed who? -A cop. a lady and a guy.
一个警察一个女人一个男人?  那不是屠杀吗  你看到了
A cop, a lady and a guy? that's a massacre. you saw it?
不是  是个男人
No, it was just a guy.
-那女的怎么了  -不  不
-what happened to the lady? -no. no.
女人  一个女警和一个男人杀了另一个男人
A woman. a policewoman and a guy, another guy, shot another guy
一个亚洲人  在窗户那  在该死的泰德家
an asian guy, in the window, at fucking Ted's house.
那个男的是泰德?
Whoa, was the other guy Ted?
不知道  他是个大块头  多毛的家伙
I don't know. he was a big, gray-haired man
他穿着长袍,开枪杀了他
and he had a robe and he shot him.
那个人脑浆四射  我要吐了
And his brain flew every I'm gonna be I'm gonna throw up.
什么?
What?
-那些炸鸡肉  -真恶心
-That was chicken fries. -sick.
你吐到我打印机上了
You threw up on my printer.
-是  -你叫了吗?
-I did. -did you break it?
-我希望没有  -听着
-I hope not. -listen, man.
我想那个人是泰德
I think the guy was Ted.
亚洲人住在市区21号
And the asians are number-two in town
你看到泰德也在其中
so you saw Ted capping the competition.
他们知道我看到他们杀人
They saw me seeing them shoot the guy.
什么?  他们看到你了?
What? they saw you?
那你他妈的还来这里?
And you fucking came here?
-他们有跟踪你到这里吗?  -不知道
-Did they follow you here? -I don't know.
-他们跟来了吗?  -我不知道不知道  听着
-Did they follow you here? -I don't know. look. look. okay.
我看到他们杀人
I saw them kill him.
我当时吓傻了  惊慌失措
I freaked out. I panicked, okay?
我把烟扔了
I tossed my roach.
-在2部车中间乱撞  -然后
-I crashed into two cars. -yeah.
他们肯定听到  他们知道有人在外面
So they must have heard they know someone was out there.
-他们知道有人看到  -他们知道是有人
-they know someone saw. -they know "someone."
但不知道是你  对吧?
They don't know it was you. right?
我不不知道
I don't I mean, yeah. I don't know.
-是的  -希望他们不知道
-yes. -I hope not.
放松
Relax.
歇会儿
Just sit back.
来享受人间罕见的大烟吧
Get ready to enjoy some of the rarest weed known to mankind.
真的罕见吗?
Is it really that rare?
极其罕见
It's, like, the rarest.
抽它真丢人
It's almost a shame to smoke it.
就像用原子弹
It's like killing a unicorn
杀了只独角兽
with, like, a bomb.
你是市里唯一有这个东西的人吗
Are you the only guy in town who has this?
-真的是独家销售?  -是的
-You're actually the only guy? -yeah.
我的伙计瑞德说给我个独家销售
My guy Red said he was giving me an exclusive sneak preview.
我是你这东西的唯一买家?  另外一些家伙拿的是大麻?
I'm the only guy you sold it to? the other guys got snicklefritz?
是  我们都是独一无二
Yeah. so we're, like, the only guys.
瑞德是从泰德那搞到的?
And Red got this from Ted?
泰德真厉害
Ted's the man.
快离开这里  快走!  快走!
Let's get the fuck out of here! go! go! let's go! let's go!
我在泰德房子外边扔了烟头
I threw a roach of this outside of Ted's house.
那又怎么样  我满大街扔烟头
So what? I throw roaches all over town.
不  他找到烟头会说  "是"菠萝快车
No. he could find the roach and say, "it's pineapple express.
索尔是唯一有菠萝快车的人
Saul is the only guy who has pineapple express.
他肯定目击了凶手案  干掉他"
He must have seen the murder! let's kill him!"
-快离开这里!  -妈的!
-Let's get out of here! -fuck!
等等!  拿大烟!  拿大烟!
Wait! stop! get weed! get the weed!
带上我们可能需要的  快餐  水果卷
Anything we might need. snacks, food, fruit roll-ups.
-快离开这里!  -好  好
-Let's get the fuck out of here! -okay, okay.
瑞德说他会在这里
Red said he'd be here.
有大麻
Them some drugs.
这房子真叫人恶心
Smells like vomit in this house.
要吗  还有一小口
Want a hit, man? it's still lit.
我得跟我老婆吃晚饭  她会知道的
I'm having dinner with my wife. she can tell.
从我毛衣上闻得出
Smell it on my sweater.
真的?
For real?
是  真的
Yeah, for real.
要穿我背心吗?  挺好闻的
You wanna wear my vest? it smell good.
不是我的风格
Not my style.
你还有风格啊  娘娘腔
You ain't got no style, motherfucker.
您拨打了语音信箱
You have reached the voice mailbox of
-泰德  -泰德  我是布达罗福斯
-Ted. -Ted, it's Budlofsky.
-我们到了  索尔跑了  -还有麦斯
-we're here. saul's gone. -and Mathe
-麦斯森  -我想他知道我们会来
-and Matheson. -I think he knew we were coming.
泰德  他们不在这里
They not here, Ted.
泰德
Hi,Ted.
好了  你了解泰德吗?
Okay, what do you know about Ted?
我觉得他是个杀人狂
I think he's crazy about murdering.
糟透了  我们能去哪里?
Well, that's not good. where are we gonna go?
去汽车旅馆  或者酒店藏起来
Let's just go go to a motel or a hotel and just hide out.
警察都介入  如果用信用卡
The police were in on it. could have flagged credit cards.
他们会找到我们的
They'll find us.
妈的  我们无路可逃
Shit. I wish we could just go nowhere.
好了
Okay.
就算他找到烟头  他怎么知道你在哪里?
Even if he found that roach, how could he know where you are?
热导飞弹
Heat-seeking missiles.
侦探犬
Bloodhounds.
狐狸
Foxes.
攻击性核潜艇
Barracudas.
你那么说真让我刮目相看  好奇怪
I'm kind of flabbergasted when you say things like that. it's weird.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
不是恭维  提个问题
Not a compliment. here's the question.
就算他找到烟头
Let's say he actually found the roach.
他怎么会把你跟菠萝快车联系在一起?
How could he connect the pineapple express weed to you?
他不能  只有他妈的瑞德知道
He can't, man. only fucking Red knows.
只有瑞德知道
Only Red knows, man.
谁是瑞德
Who is Red?
瑞德是我跟泰德的中间人
Red's, like, the middleman between, like, Ted and me.
我们就像是铁哥们
And we're, like, mad fucking tight, man.
有一次  他找了个女孩
One time, he got this girl
见面不到5分钟就给我打飞机
to give me a hand job, like, within five minutes of meeting her.
就像  我都不知道你叫什么名字
It was like, "i don't even know your name, whoa."
听起来挺酷  要是问
That is pretty rad, but, like
你把菠萝快车卖给谁了吗?
"Did you sell the pineapple express to anyone?"
他会说  "是的我卖给了索尔"  他为何不说?
He'll be, "yeah, I sold it to Saul." why wouldn't he?
不  不  我操
No. oh, no. fuck that, man.
戴尔  操他妈的打飞机  想想如果我给你打飞机
Fucking hand job, dale. imagine if I gave you a hand job.
-我为何要那样  -不  我是说如果
-why would I wanna do that? -no, I mean if I got you a hand job.
对瑞德不起作用  他是个毒贩
The same rules don't apply to Red. he's a drug dealer.
我也是毒贩  你是说你不相信我吗?
I'm a drug dealer. are you saying you don't trust me?
不是  那不是我想说的  我?
No, that's not at all what I'm you know what?
忽略我刚说的话吧  打电话给他  打给他
You know? just ignore what I said. call him. give him a call.
看看情况如何
See what the dealio is.
-喂  -瑞德  还好吗?
-hello. -hey,Red, you okay?
索尔  还可以  就是脚趾骨折
Yeah,Saul. yeah, I'm fine, man. I just stubbed my toe.
小心点  在屋子里穿鞋
Be careful, man. be careful. wear shoes in the house.
安全  安全第一  合作第二  听着
Safety. safety first, then teamwork. now, listen.
你知道你给我的菠萝快车吗?
You know that pineapple express stuff you gave me?
别告诉别人你卖给我了
Don't tell anybody that you sold it to me.
我不会跟任何人
I'd never talk to anyone
讲有关我们做毒品交易的事
about the stuff that I do with you involving drugs.
好的  听着我想过去一趟
All right, cool. listen, I'm gonna come by.
我得跟你发泄发泄
I gotta lay some shit on you.
一粒老鼠屎坏了一锅汤
There is a fly in the ointment.
老鼠撞枪口上  狮子要发威
Shit has hit the fan. the lion will speak.
-我腹背受敌  -不  严肃点
-I'm in the middle of a convo. -no, seriously.
-我们半个小时内到  -好极了
-We're gonna be there in half an hour. -perfect.
-不要  不  不  -我们先去那里避避风头
-no, please. no, no, no. -let's go over there and chill out.
不  我们明天去行吗  我们都来这里了
No, can we go tomorrow? look, we're already here
电话那头还有一个人
There's somebody else on the phone with him.
-谁?  -不知道
-who? -I don't know.
他在跟另一个人在那窃窃私语
He's whispering to another man.
我们早上去  那样好一点
We'll go in the morning. it's better that way.
-好的  -好  好  谢谢
-okay. -yes. yes. thank you. yes.
你们明天来是吗
so you're coming by tomorrow?
你怎么知道?
How'd you know that?
听到你小声跟另一个人说的
Heard you whispering to that other guy that you were talking to.
谁啊
Who is that?
是的  戴尔  不错啊  听着  我早上去不了
Right, dale. good job. listen, I can't go in the morning
因为我的妞儿该给她调闹钟的  已是夏令时
because my bubbe gotta change her clocks. daylight-savings.
是住在河街41号的那个妞儿吗?
Is that the bubbe that's on 41 st and river street?
我们一起玩推圆盘游戏的地方
The one where we played shuffleboard that one time?
知道了  我们要中午到
You got it. so, listen, we'll be chilling by noon.
-中午到  同志  -挺好
-noon it is, bromosexual. -nice.
我们该再去一次赌场  待一会儿
We should hit up the casino again. it's been a while.
好的  我们一定要去赌场
Okay, yeah. we'll definitely hit the casino up.
一定  好的  当心  兄弟
Definitely. all right, peace, brother.
我得赶紧打电话给安吉
I should call Angie soon.
编点谎言
Make up some bullshit.
我冷
I'm cold.
-你冷吗  -我一点也不冷  给
-You're cold? -oh, I'm not cold at all. here.
很热
I run hot.
-真的?  -真的
-really? -yeah.
-你脂肪厚  -血液多  穿上吧
-you got more body mass. -thick blood. yeah, no, take it.
-谢谢  -我不怎么喜欢  不过没关系
-thank you. -I don't appreciate that, but it's okay.
我得打电话给安吉
I'm gonna call Angie.
太空
Space.
戴尔  等等
Dale, wait. wait.
电话  电话
The phones. the phones.
-你说他们是警察  是吧  -是
-you said they were cops, right? -they are, yeah.
我在想也许他们能
I was thinking, maybe they can
破解这些东西或者追踪我们
triangulate these things, man, or, like, trace them.
-是吗  -他们就是这么找到萨达姆的
-Right? -that's how they got Saddam.
-对  -妈的  你说得对
-right. -fuck. you're right, man.
他们都能跟踪他们
Maybe they can even trace them
那我们就不要用这些了
like, when we're not even on them, you know?
或许可以把它们埋起来
Maybe if we bury them
接收不到  他们就没办法了
The reception will cut off and they won't be able to.
我们可以把它们弄到动物身上  转移目标
We can tie it to an animal, be a diversion.
我们抓不到动物
We'll never catch an animal.
树上有松鼠  它们会认为我们是
The squirrel'd be up in a tree, they'd think we were.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
-我们要弄个热气球然后  -不行
-We'll build a hot-air balloon and -no.
-把它们摔碎  -好  好的
-We'll smash them. -yeah, yeah.
我要把它摔碎  往石头上摔
I'm gonna smash it. on a rock.
-这里  好点子  -好主意  好的  毁了它
-Right here. good thinking. -good idea. yes, destroy it.
-就这样  -去死吧
-Get it. -die. yes.
-怎么回事  -我本想往树上砸的  没砸到
-What the fuck was that? -I was trying to hit that tree. I missed.
-什么树?  -那棵
-what tree? -that one.
为何你就不能像正常人一样往石头上摔
Why didn't you smash it on a rock like a normal person?
不知道  人们又不经常砸东西?  我脑子生锈啊
I don't know. how often does somebody smash things? I'm rusty.
你看到手机掉哪里了吗
Did you at least see where it landed?
我不知道  打一下
I don't know. call it.
打一下?  用什么打?  我的手机已经摔坏了
Call it? with what? my phone has been smashed.
我猜他们连破解都办不到
I bet they can't even triangulate those things.
你一下说可以  一下又说不行
Well, you convinced me they can. you were very convincing back there.
好了  我去找  妈的
Hey. fine. I'll go find it. fuck.
-看到了吗?  -看到什么?
-Do you see it? -see what?
手机啊  白痴
The phone, you idiot.
我们干吗来这里  这个地方太吓人了
Why are we here? this place is so fucking scary.
至少我有点子  你没有  闭嘴吧
At least I had an idea. you didn't, so shut up.
不是这样  我有两个主意  天涯和海角
That's not true. I had two ideas. nowhere and quiznos.
-什么?  -那是什么?
-What? -What was that?
-What? -What is that?
-什么?  -有声音
-What? -I hear something.
什么?
What?
我不清楚  你听到了吗?
I don't know. do you hear that?
伙计  我真的什么都没听到
Dude, I literally hear nothing.
妈的!
Oh, fuck!
你去哪?  你跑什么啊?  回来!
Where are you going? what are you running from? return to me now!
救命!
Help me!
让他滚远点!
Tell him to get away from me!
我怕黑!  我投降!
I'm scared of this darkness! I surrender!
-滚开!  滚开!  -我手无寸铁!
-Go away! go away! -I'm unarmed!
-这一点都不好玩!  -戴尔!
-This isn't funny anymore! -Dale!
-撤退!  -救命!
-Fall back! -Save me!
妈的
Oh, shit.
车
Car.
开门!  快开门!
Open it! open it! open the door! open it!
-快开锁  -我打不开
-Unlock it. -I can't unlock it.
你干什么呢  小心点里边的东西
What are you doing? watch the upholstery.
-快走!  我看到了!  -没!  你看到什么了?  闭嘴!
-Go! I saw something! -no! what did you see? shut up!
他妈的给我闭嘴!
Shut the fuck shut up, man!
我听到了  然后又看到
I heard something, then I saw something.
你什么都没有听到
You didn't hear anything, man.
我看到了
Well, I saw something.
你能说说那个穿着贴身短裤的人
And you're telling me that guy in the little short shorts
-怎么打断你鼻子的?  -好的
- broke your nose? -right.
那个神秘人打断了你的鼻子吗?  汉子?
The bedazzler guy broke your nose, tough man?
醒醒  起来  醒醒
Wake up. get up. wake up.
我怎么趴你身上了?
How did I get on you?
我也好奇
I wonder.
手表终于坏掉了
Watch finally broke.
烦死了  现在几点了?
Crazy. what time is it?
不对吧
That can't be right.
怎么会是凌晨3点  这可能吗?
It couldn't be 3 in the morning, could it?
现在3点了?
It's 3:00 right now?
伙计  这下坏事了!
Holy shit, man!
我们本该中午就到瑞德那里的
We were supposed to be at Red's at noon, man.
要是他走了?  我们什么信息都得不到怎么办
What if he's gone? If we didn't get any information
不对  现在是夏令时  所以
No, it's daylight-savings, so
-所以现在才2点  -不对  不对  是拨快一个小时
-So it's only 2:00. -Oh, no, it went forward an hour.
现在他妈已经4点了  完蛋了  不  兄弟  这下坏了
It's 4 o'-fucking-clock? fuck me. no, man. that's bad.
妈的  我们大概睡了有18个小时
Shit. we slept for, like, 18 hours.
我的兄弟兄弟该气炸了
My Bubbe man, my Bubbe's gonna be so pissed.
妈的
Shit.
我们要打电话给瑞德
We gotta call Red.
是啊  用什么打?
Okay. how?
我们去找个电话亭
We'll go to a pay phone.
不  不行  他的号码在我手机里
No, I can't. his number is in my phone.
太棒了  那你还记得他住哪里吗?
Great. well, do you remember where he lives?
当然  我当然知道他住哪里
Yeah, I know where he lives.
你是在暗示我是个健忘的人吗?
What are you insinuating? like, I'm forgetful?
"暗示"  是个好词儿
"insinuating." good word.
你知道是什么意思吗?
Do you know what that means?
-我当然知道 不管你信不信  -意思像是"看起来像"
-I do know what that means believe it or not. -It means, like, "to seem like."
开车啊  我受够这森林了  走吧
Let's roll. I'm done with the woods. let's go.
快点开车  离开这该死的地方
Come on, Let's get the fuck out of here.
好的  我们走吧  不  发动不了  电池没了
Okay. let's go. no. it's not working. the battery's dead.
等等
Wait.
电池没了是什么意思?
What do you mean, it's dead?
什么意思?  就是说电池没了  玩完了
What do I mean? I mean the battery's dead. the battery's dead.
你到底在说些什么啊?
What do you mean, the battery's dead?
我要怎样换个方式解释呢?
How can I explain this to you differently?
电池没了就是它停止运作了
The battery is dead. it ceased to live.
它不会动了  索尔  车需要有电池才能发动
It's deceased now. The car needs a battery to start, Saul.
这一切都是怎么发生的啊?
How did this happen?
显然  我们忘记熄火就睡着了  然后就
Well, we clearly fell asleep with the battery on, and
天啊  在上"抓狂电台"吗?
Oh, man. to talk radio?
-是啊  "抓狂电台"  -老兄  太无聊了
-Yes, talk radio. -It's so boring, man.
-好的  好的  -这辆车刚刚自杀了
-Okay, okay. -The car just committed suicide.
你闭嘴  我有个点子
Shut up, man. I have an idea now.
我们要走了
We gonna go.
我们走到路上  搭个顺风车
We'll walk back to the road. we'll hitchhike.
有人会载我们到瑞德那里的
Someone will pick us up, take us to Red's.
瑞德会告诉我们一切都好  一切回归正轨
Red will tell us everything's fine, everything will go back to normal.
听起来不错吧?
How does that sound? good?
-这是个好主意  -再接再厉
-that's a good idea. -keep our heads on strarght.
继续这样思考问题  我们就他妈轻松了
If we just keep thinking like this, we're fucking gravy.
-好的  那就听你的  -我们走吧
-all right. I'm in. -let's do it.
-我能要回我的夹克吗?  －当然
-Can I have my jacket back, please? -Yeah.
-谢谢你  -谢谢你才对
-Thank you. -thank you.
谢谢你帮我保管它
Thanks for taking care of it.
看那  我的拇指就像我弟弟
Look, it's like my thumb is my cock.
那样拦不到车  哥儿们
That's not gonna get us a ride, man.
到这里就行了
Here's good.
谢尔德  谢谢你载我们一程
Thanks for the smooth sailing, Sharid.
不客气
You're welcome.
-他可靠吗?  -瑞德
-You're sure we can trust this guy? -yo, Red.
谁啊?
Who is it?
-是布鲁斯  -布鲁斯?  他妈的是谁啊?
-it's bruce. -bruce? who the fuck is this?
-索尔  怎么了?  -你以为是谁啊?
-Saul. what's up? -Who do you think it is?
这个人是谁啊?
Who's this?
我是戴尔  瑞德先生  非常高兴见到你
I'm dale, Mr. Red. nice to meet you.
没有姓吗?
Dale who?
你还是不知道我全名的好
It's best if you don't know my full name.
戴尔·丹顿  不用担心  他跟我一道的
Dale Denton. don't worry, he's with me.
戴尔·丹顿  兄弟  见到你很高兴
Dale denton. nice to meet you, bro.
-等一下  我把门打开?  -赶紧啊
-Hold on. Let me get this lock, okay? -You better.
-快进来  -进来了
-Get in here. -Coming in.
-你们都想买点毒品吗?  -来搜身吧
-Y'all wanna buy some drugs? -Frisk me.
-最近怎么样?  最近怎么样?  -找到了吗
-What's up? what's up? -Get it.
瞧这个?
Look at that, huh?
-朋友们  最近好吗?  -你怎么样了?
-What's up, players? -What's up?
我在申请那讨厌的奖学金  冷静点
I've been up in here trying to get a motherfucking scholarship. chilling.
那衣服是怎么回事啊?
What's up with the clothes?
我们去露营了
We were camping.
-去露营了?  -是啊
-camping? -yeah.
朋友  你的嘴唇没事吧?
Is your lip okay, man?
-你哭过了?  -我的嘴唇
-you been crying? -oh, my lip.
就是冻疮啦
It's a cold sore.
以前从未如此  所以我就哭了
Never had one before, so I started to cry.
尽管你们认为这比看起来糟是很普通的
U think it's a lot worse than it looks, though. quite simple kind of
你得的是可恶的疱疹吗?
Is that means fucking herpes?
是的  没错
Yeah. yes, it does.
那可真恶心  老兄  你知道我们可能会被传染吗
Fucking sick, man. you know how many joints we've shared?
我知道  我是个恶心的人
I know. I'm a disgusting person.
兄弟  疱疹可医不好
Herpes is for life, bro.
我肯定要在上面抹点药膏的
I'm gonna try to definitely put some sort of medical ointment on it.
我已经用了维柯丁止痛药  但是不管用啊
I have been taking vicodin. doesn't really take swelling down.
是因为那一次  老兄  我可警告过你啊
It's from that time. I told you, man.
你吃了从脱衣舞女郎那里抢来的棒棒糖  是你自找的
You wonna eat that lollipop out of that stripper's snatch. you wanted to do it.
从她阴道里拿出来的  还记得你做了什么吗  你做了什么
Out of her vagina. remember what you did? what did you do?
-什么都没有  -你吃了一盒从她屁眼拿出来的鼻涕虫
-Nothing,-You ate a box of nerds out of her butthole.
你他妈不是说不会再提起了吗  自食其果
You fucking said you wouldn't tell. you sowed your own poison, man.
伙计们  认真点  我们来是有事的  问他啊
Dudes, seriously, we're here for a reason. just ask him.
冷静点  我煮了点鸡蛋  我们有的是时间
Chill. I'm boiling some eggs over here. we got a lot of time to hang out.
-我他妈在做蛋糕  -少扯淡
-I'm making a fucking cake. -no shit.
我可以来一块吗?
Can I have a piece of that?
-别只顾着吃了  -我连一块都不能吃吗?
-Don't ask for a piece. -I can't have a piece?
不  你不能吃  这是很私人的
No, you can't. this is private.
知道今天是什么日子吗?
Do you know what today is?
-是星期二  -今天是我家猫的生日
-Tuesday. -This is my cat's birthday today.
我没见到猫啊  不好意思  你把它放出去了?
I don't see a cat in here. I'm sorry. You let it out by accident?
没有  他3个月前就死了  可以了吧?
No, because he died three months ago, okay?
那现在谁比较幽默?
So now who's the funny guy?
对不起
Sorry.
今天是他的生日
Today is his birthday
他的生日传统是
and it is a tradition that on his birthday
我提前起床为他做他最爱吃的甜点
I get up extra early and make him his favorite kind of dessert.
别担心  兄弟  你的猫会上天堂的
Don't worry, bro. Your cat's going to heaven.
可能吧  他也许会下地狱的
Yeah, maybe. maybe he went to heaven.
他很可恶  他可能已经滚去地狱了
He was a little fucker. He could've gone to hell.
为什么我们在讨论伙计们
What are we talk? guys
问他  直接问他好吗?
Ask him. Just ask him, okay?
想问什么  直接点  怎么了?
Ask what? Just come straight. What's up?
-那好吧  -问他
-Yeah right. -Lay it on him.
我们想了解一下
We need to know
我们想了解你的上家
We need to know about your source.
-泰德  -泰德·琼斯
-Ted. -Ted Jones.
瞧  戴尔是个传票传送员
See, Dale, here, is a protest servant.
我不是  我不是干那个的
I'm not. that's not what I am.
他不是  但他在泰德的房子外面
He's not that, but he was outside Ted's house
别说了我们不想把你也卷进来  知道吗?
Don't look, we don't want to bring you in to what we're in, okay?
你不想惹麻烦  我们也不会给你带来麻烦
You don't want any trouble. we don't wanna give you trouble.
所以最好你别管发生了什么事
It's probably best you don't know the whole story.
-你认为我不能处理危机吗?  -你在说什么啊?
-You don't think I can handle danger? -What are you talking about?
-你当然能  -我完全可以处理
-You can. -I totally can.
至于你们  进来我家
And for you to come into my house
自以为帮我而不告诉我秘密
and not tell secrets because you think you're saving me
事实上  这么做只让你们变成了大傻瓜
well, in reality, it just makes you look like a dumb-ass.
看这儿  看到了吗?
Look at this. see this?
看到了没有  我可一根腋毛都没有?
You see that? there's no hair under here, okay?
那能说明什么?
What's the significance of that?
当我打架的时候就少点阻力  我能处理危机
It makes me aerodynamic when I fight. I can take danger.
那好吧  有人打电话来问索尔或菠萝快车的事吗?
Okay, has anyone called asking about Saul or the pineapple express?
我们就想知道这些
That's all we need to know.
是有还是没有?
Is it "uh-huh" or "uh-uh"?
-是"没有"  -就是这个  伙计
-It's "uh-uh." -There it is, man.
多明白啊  都结束了
Cleared. over.
一切都很好  我都告诉过你了  兄弟
Everything's fine. I told you, bro.
我们在林子里过了一个荒谬的夜晚
We had a wacky night in the woods
但是我们应该像个大人一样把那些给忘了
but we both can put that behind us like adults.
现在我们该抽点大麻  庆祝下了
Now it's time to get super-duper high.
我在特拉维夫拿的烟枪有吗?
Got that bong I got in tel aviv?
有啊  点上吧
"bong mitzvah." hit it up.
好的
Yes.
你满意了吧
There you go.
为什么不听他的  放松点?
Why don't you follow his lead and chill out?
已经放松了  伙计  我现在泰然自若
I'm chill. I'm chill as a cucumber, man.
-你看上去可不怎么放松  -比你放松多了
-You don't seem chill. -More chill than you.
你比我还放松?
You're more chill than me?
看我穿着什么  和服  你穿着什么?
Look at what I'm wearing. kimono. what are you wearing?
-西装  -就是说啊
-Suit. -Yeah. exactly.
我不知道你发生了什么事  但是我不觉得我喜欢你
I don't know what's up with you, but I don't know if I like you.
老兄  我也不觉得我喜欢你
Well I don't know if I like you either, man.
那就是你的损失  因为我会是很棒的朋友
Well, that's your loss, because I'm a great friend.
我要打电话给我老婆了  可以吗?
I'm gonna use the telefono to call my wife, okay?
-打吧  -马上打
-give her a call. -I will.
-打吧  -可别偷听我说的话哦
-go ahead. -don't pay attention to what I'm saying.
我当然不会
Oh I won't.
瞎说
Bullshit.
不  不要  不要
No, no, no.
-谎话精  -伙计  你在干什么
-Liar. -What are you doing, man?
老兄  他就是个谎话精  他对我们撒谎了
He's a liar. he's lying to us, man. He's lying to us.
不  他没有
No, he's not.
他知道我的名字  他行为古怪
He knows my name. he's acting weird.
伙计  我们不能让他给任何人打电话
We can't let him phone anyone, man.
你疯啦  你太多疑了  把电话给他
Freaking out. you're paranoid. give him the phone.
先生  我不信任你
I do not trust you, sir.
-你太多疑了  -他的行为古怪
-You're paranoid. -He's acting weird.
瑞德  伙计  对不起
Red, I'm sorry, bro.
-上帝啊  -我操
-Jesus! -Holy cock.
我操
Fuck you!
你在干什么  他都说对不起了
What are you doing, man? he's sorry.
老天啊
Oh, jesus.
疱疹!
Herpes!
我不想那么做的
I don't wanna have to do this.
瑞德  伙计  你疯了啊
Red, you're crazy, man.
你把个混蛋弄进了我家
You brought the devil into my house.
-我们是朋友啊  -我知道
-We're friends. -I know we are.
-这就是为什么感觉很糟  -你又吸食安非他命了?
-That's why it sucks. -Are you on meth again?
戴尔  他在打我!
Dale, he's hurting me!
厕所
Toilet.
冲掉
Flush.
人生虽然有限  但是个人作为的影响却是深远的
What we do in this life echoes in eternity.
说的对!
True!
他要打电话给泰德!
He's going for the phone to call Ted!
给我待在外面!
Stay out of here!
瑞德  不要那么做!
Red, don't do it!
-瑞德!  -卑鄙的家伙
-Red! -You assholes.
你们毁了我的手提电话
You ruined my portable phone.
-一起撞  -好的
-Teamwork. -Yes.
你们要把门撞坏  你们会赔给我吗?
You're gonna break the door. gonna pay for it?
妈的
Fuck.
踩扁电话
Phone.
-放开我!  放开我!  把我放开!  -他妈的
-Let go! let go! let go! -What the hell?
把我放开  把这扇天杀的门从我身上弄开!
I let go, now just get this goddamn door off of me!
坦白从宽!
Tell us everything, now!
如果说了他们会杀了我的
Said they were gonna kill me.
你对泰德说了些什么?
What did you tell Ted?
他要把我的蛋蛋压碎了  要把我的蛋蛋压碎了
He's crushing my balls. crushing my balls.
压扁它们
Smash them.
他妈的!
Fuck!
休战
Time out. time out.
-休战  -又开始了  去你妈的
-Truce. -Time in. fuck you.
-停下!  -骗人精!
-Stop! -Cheater!
-抱歉  抱歉  我很抱歉  -瑞德!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -Red!
-抱歉  抱歉  -到
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -get
他妈的
Fuck.
天哪
God
他妈的!
Fuck!
-接着  王八蛋!  -休战!
-Take it motherfucker! -Time out!
操!
Fuck!
不!  不要啊!
No! no, no, no!
你想去哪里啊?
Where you going, huh?
你以为你要去哪里啊  扭扭先生?
Where do you think you're going, mr. wiggles?
-来吧  给我回来  -索尔  救我!  救我!
-Come on. get back here. -Saul, help me! help me!
他在捶我的屁股!
He's punching my bum!
我受够了  我们来把事情说清楚  动口别动手了
I'm done with this. let's talk. let's try words.
动口别动手了  不!  不!  不!
Use words! no! no! no!
你还好吗  朋友
You okay, man?
-我会再给你一个烟枪  -今天是我猫的生日
-I'll get you another bong. -It's my cat's birthday.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
-行吗?  -谢谢你
-all right? -thank you.
我想信箱里有个包裹
I think there's a package in the mailbox.
这一切都结束了!
This ends now!
该死
Oh, shit.
这会太过了吗?
Was that too much?
找不到开口
Can't get the edge.
等等  好了  弄好了
Wait. got it. got it.
戴尔
Hey, Dale.
要杀了他吗?  我可没这个能耐
Think we're gonna have to kill him? I don't think I'm capable of murder.
我也没有
I don't think I am either.
也许我们能说服他自杀
Maybe we could just convince him to kill himself.
或者  什么都别说
Or, just not say anything.
我们得了解他都知道点什么?
We need to find out everything he knows, okay?
醒醒
Wake up.
发生什么事了  朋友?
Hey, what's up, dudes?
发生什么事了?  把你知道的一切都告诉我们
What's up? tell us everything now.
说话呀  瑞德
Talk, Red.
我要活动活动  从这里逃出去
I'm gonna flex and bust out of here.
绑结实了
Trapped.
别妄想了  瑞德
Not happening, Red.
那好吧  我坦白
Okay. all right. okay, I'll talk.
泰德·琼斯  他知道你们目睹了杀人经过  找到了你的大麻烟蒂
Ted Jones, he knows you witnessed the murder. he found your roach.
他派了两个人过来  布达罗福斯和麦斯森
He sent two guys over here, Budlofsky and Matheson.
俩狗娘养的大个子
Two real big son of a bitches.
是来杀你们的
They're basically out to kill you guys.
如果我不把你们供出来  他们就会杀了我
They're gonna kill me too, unless I turn y'all over.
所以你们俩基本上就死定了
So you guys are basically fucked.
有多少个警察被他收买了?  告诉我们
How many cops does he have on his payroll? tell us.
-有个女的警察  卡罗尔  -就是那个女警
-Well,there's the woman cop, Carol. -That's the lady cop.
我不清楚  他可能有一堆  这家伙关系可多了
I don't know. He could have a bunch. This dude is super well-connected.
他还有个很厉害的藏身之处  是个十足的坏蛋
And he has a really awesome hideout too. it's pretty badass.
-妈的  -还有什么?
-Oh, shit. -What else?
他现在和亚洲人有场战争
He's at a war right now with the asians.
他们正在进行毒品战争
They're in a drug war right now.
亚洲人  什么亚洲人?  印度人也算是亚洲人
Asians? what asians? indians are technically asian.
-那倒是真的  -什么亚洲人?
-It's true. -What asians?
我不知道  可能是中国人  可能是韩国人
I don't know. what? chinese? or korean or
越南人?
Vietcong?
是啊  就是小小个子亚洲人
Yeah, little just little asian people.
一个  有枪有毒品的亚洲人  但不是他的朋友
Like, the asians with the guns and the drugs, and not his friends.
-开门  -瑞德  开门
-Ding-dong. -Hey, Red!
-这下完了  -他们来了
-Oh, shit. -oh, they're here.
他们是来杀我的
They're here to kill me.
我知道我出卖了你们
Okay, I know I sold y'all out.
我是狗娘养的烂朋友
I've been a son of a bitch and a shitty friend.
索尔  我在和你说话呀  戴尔  你是我的新朋友
Saul, I'm talking to you. Dale, you're a new friend.
我可以弥补的  我忘记了"为兄弟两肋插刀"
I can make it up. I forgot, "bro's before ho's."
从后门离开  我什么都不会说的
Just go out the back porch. I won't say anything.
-我会掩护你们的  -谢啦
-I'll cover for you. -thanks.
没问题的
No sweat.
是戴尔·丹顿  戴尔·丹顿和索尔
It was Dale Denton. Dale Denton and Daul.
他们从后门逃了  快一步你们还可以抓住他们  快去啊
They're on the back porch. You can catch them if you hurry. go.
瞧啊  躲这里面
Hey. in here.
我们得去找个电话亭  快点
I've gotta get to a phone. come on.
-我们得藏起来  -为什么?
-we should hide. -why?
如果瑞德告诉泰德的手下我的名字的话
If Red tells Ted's guys about my name
他们就会去我的公寓
then they'll go to my apartment.
在那里  我那里有安吉的名字
There, I have Angie's name.
他们会联想到她然后去找她  快走啊
They'll put that together find her. Let's go.
不  我认为我们该留在这里
No. I think we should stay.
-为什么?  -因为我已经在垃圾箱里了
-why? -I'm in the dumpster already.
那就出来  快点  你已经脏到爆了
Well, then, get out. come on, you're already dirty.
-他们已经逃了  -那就看看他都知道点什么
-They're gone. -Well find out what he knows.
瑞德  这是你最后的机会了  兄弟
Red, it's your last chance, man.
你得告诉我们点有用的线索?
You gonna give us something we can use?
麦斯森  你不是在开玩笑吧  你还想要什么
Matheson, you gotta be kidding me. I mean, what more do you want?
我告诉过你  那个人的名字是戴尔·丹顿
I told you that the guy's name is Dale Denton.
他显然是和索尔一伙的
He's obviously working with Saul.
他们来我这儿  把我家弄得一团糟
They came in here, busted my house to shit.
还打了我一顿
They kicked the hell out of me
把我绑在我祖父的轮椅上
duct-taped me to my grandfather's wheelchair.
你还想要什么?  想让我帮你算命吗?
What more do you want? want me to read your horoscope?
-听到了吗  泰德?  -问下他们是不是亚洲人
-You hear that, ted? -Ask if either of them were asian.
-他们是什么人种?  -他们是白人
-What skin color were they? -They were white people.
丹顿可能曾是个犹太人  我也不知道
Denton might've been a jew. I don't know.
就凭那些我没法评判一个人
I don't judge people based on things like that.
显然我们是朋友
Obviously. We're friends.
泰德  听到他说的了吗?
Ted, you hear him?
戴尔·丹顿不是亚洲人  好了  干掉瑞德
Dale Denton is not asian. all right. kill Red.
如果你们俩都把鞋脱了我会很感激的
Listen, I would appreciate it if both y'all would take your shoes off.
这可是全新的地毯  你们把土都蹭到上面了
This is brand-new carpet. you're tracking mud in here.
麦斯森  你还穿着英式靴子
Matheson, you got british knights on.
自从1987年以后我就没再看到有人穿过了
I ain't seen anybody wear them since 1987.
你他妈在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
泰德叫我干掉他
Ted told me to kill him.
自控一下吧?
Well, how about a little fucking discretion here?
看吧?  看吧?  就在那里  看到了没有?
See? see? see, right there. you see that?
-你看到了吗?  -看到什么了?
-you catch it? -see what?
你以前做事也很鲁莽
You used to not give a fuck about discretion.
我见过你把人家的颚骨打脱了  我看到过
I seen you pull somebody's jawbone off. I seen it.
你太冷酷无情了
You was ruthless.
冷酷无情
You was ruthless, man.
我操  老兄?  你打中了我的腹部
What the fuck, man? you shot me in my stomach.
我现在可能快死了
I'm gonna die now probably.
我曾请你们吃过晚餐  鱼肉玉米饼
I had you all over here for dinner. fish tacos.
你们就是这样对我的吗?
This how you do me?
那布达罗福斯和麦斯森说了什么?
So, what did Budlofsky and Matheson say?
我不清楚
I don't know.
有个叫索尔的男人
There's this guy, Saul
卖大麻给一起干活的人  叫戴尔·丹顿来着
something, selling weed who works with some guy, Dale Denton.
这是他得到的所有信息
That's all he got out of him.
你觉得他和被我们弄死的人有关系吗?
Do you think he has anything to do with the guy that we shot?
那他还说了点什么?
Well, did he say anything else?
索尔有提到关于"要去赌场"
Saul mentioned something about "going to the casino."
-奇怪  -"要去赌场"?
-weird. -"going to the casino"?
泰德  赌场是归亚洲人的
The asians own the casino, Ted.
-我得再来一瓶啤酒  -他是为他们做事的
-I need another beer. -He's gotta be working for them.
也许我们杀了那家伙后  他们就雇了这个叫戴尔
Maybe after we popped that guy,they hired this outside guy,Dale
他什么名字来着?  丹顿吗?  来完成接下来的任务
What's his name? denton?  To finish the job.
也许吧
Maybe.
好吧  也许  我大概一个小时后回来
Maybe, well,I'll be back in an hour.
我会把这家伙的一切都调查清楚
I'll have everything there is to know about this dale denton guy.
包括他为谁卖命  他妈妈是谁  一切的一切
Who he's screwing, Who's his mother, everything.
我去找这个家伙
I have to take a shit.
等等我  我们要去哪儿?
Wait. Where are we going?
我想  我得去安吉家  我要确认她现在是安全的
I gotta I gotta get to angie's. I have to make sure she's okay.
那我的女人怎么办  你不觉得他们会找她麻烦吗
What about my bubbe? Don't think they'll go after her.
我的意思是她的名字很少见
I mean,she has a different last name.
叫宝格斯
Belogus.
我不知道  别站在马路中间  走
I don't know. We should get out of the middle of the road. come on.
你们俩爱等多久等多久吧
You guys can wait as long as you want
我可饿了  我要开饭了
But one minute from right now.,I'm gonna eat some food.
你们可以说我没礼貌  随你们说
And you can call it rude. You can call it whatever you want.
你们就饿着肚子保持仪态吧  但我得吃了
You can be polite with your clean plates, but I'm gonna be eating food.
老爸  他会来的
Dad, he'll be here.
我去别的房间吃  然后顺便收个电邮,我受够这些了
I'm going in the other room and eat it, check my e-mail. I'm done.
亲爱的  我们正准备吃饭  谁都别想离开桌子半步
Honey, we're at the table. No one's going to leave the table.
-好了  到了  -好极了  我们进去吧
-Okay. This is it. -All right. Let's do this.
不  不  不  我自己进去
No,no,no. I'm going alone.
-不是吧  -是的  就是这样
-No. -Yeah. Yeah.
-我还想见见安吉呢  -以后会有机会的
-I wanna meet angie. -You'll meet her later man. look.
听着  我要你在外面守着  好吗?
Look,I need you to stay out here. Keep guard,okay?
-这很重要  你就在这守着  -好吧
-It's important. watch my back. -Okay.
-谢谢  -好吧  你表现得好点
-Thanks. -All right. Just be yourself.
我守着呢
I'll keep guard.
天哪
Shit.
不是吧
Oh no.
你好啊  戴尔
Hey dale.
你好  戴尔
Hello dale
晚饭
Dinner.
我记得你邀请我来吃晚饭的  就是今晚
This is the dinner you invited me to. That was tonight.
所以我来了
That's why I'm here.
请坐吧
Sit. please.
好的  你好
Of course. Hi.
-你好啊  -我是莎安侬
-Hi. -Shannon.
-介绍下  -见到你很高兴
-Intros. -Great to meet you.
-如果我没记错  你是罗伯特吧  -请坐  可以开饭了
-Robert,If I'm not mistaken. -Sit down,so we can eat.
-你好  戴尔  -好了
-Hi dale. -Hey. okay.
-你怎么了?  -没事啊
-What happened to you? -Nothing.
我现在就该来这儿
I'm supposed to be here right now.
所以我来了
So I'm here.
-你很脏  还在流血  -没有啊  我是来吃饭的
-You're all dirty and bleeding. -No,I'm not. I'm here for dinner.
-你额头上还有抓痕  -伙计  你闻起来恶心极了
-You have scratches on your forehead. -Dude,you smell like shit.
-戴尔  你到底怎么了?  -我去树林里了
-Dale,what happened to you? -I was in the woods.
-去树林?  -是的  很奇怪是不是  我是去
-In the woods? -Yeah. Isn't that weird? I was
-我是去树林里了  -你去那里干嘛?
-I was in the woods. -What were you doing?
我去观察鸟类  不  我没去
I bird-watch. I don't.
事实上我没去  我得实话实说了
No I don't. Look,I'm gonna come clean.
我目击了一起谋杀案?
I witnessed a murder okay?
我看到有人杀了人
I saw someone murder someone else
我觉得他们正在跟踪我
and I think they've been following me.
他们很可能去我的公寓
There's a good chance they went to my apartment
那里到处都是跟安吉有关的东西
where angie has a lot of things.
她的毕业纪念册  成绩单  电话号码
Her yearbooks,report cards,her cell number is written
就写在我冰箱上
and it's on my fridge.
然后他们会找到这里  他们会来这里
So they could then find this house. They could come here.
那我们现在就报警
We should call the police right away.
我们不能报警  警察是凶手之一
We can't. The police were the murderers.
我们不能报警  因为警察是凶手
We can't call the police. They were the murderers.
安吉  我向上帝发誓  你得做些什么  而我要去
Angie,I swear to god.you do something or I'm gonna
-真是糟透了  -不  不要让他光想
-So fucked up. -No. don't let him "gonna."
不要光想  听着  我们现在就得离开这里
No,don't wanna. Look,we gotta get the f out of here.
快走  我们得提前撤退啊
Let's go. We need to begin to prematurely evacuate.
-你是不是吸毒了?  -你说什么  我没有吸毒啊  为什么这么说
-Are you high? -What? no. I'm not high. why?
我看你是吸毒吸得飘飘然了
You are high as a fucking kite.
我可没吸毒  我们快走
I'm not high. Let's go.
我们不走  我马上回来
We're not going. I'm coming back in a minute.
你知道我去干什么吗  去拿枪
You know what I'm coming back with? with a gun.
你最好快走  我可不会跟你一起走
You better be out. I'm not fucking with you.
你要去拿枪?  他的枪?
Your gun? his gun?
别去拿枪  他为什么要去拿武器呢?
Why do you? Don't get a gun. Why would he bear arms?
我们得走了  我来带头
No,we need to go. everyone.I'm leading the parade.
-这太让人激动了  -好了  好了
-This is so exciting. -Okay Okay.
这是你们的车库吗  我们准备出发了
Is this where you're parked? Let's sally forth.
到底是谁在跟踪你  还有安吉?
Who is after you,after angie?
是一群毒贩  据我所知是他们是贩毒的
They're drug dealers. I have reason to believe that they're drug dealers.
你在说什么啊  你疯了
What are you talking about? you're out of your mind.
-我知道这听起来很疯狂  -快躲起来
-I know it sounds crazy. -Hide.
戴尔  戴尔  戴尔  他们来了  我刚才正吃着水果卷
Dale! dale! dale! it's happening. I was eating a fruit roll
-你干吗啊?  -上帝啊!
-Why'd you do that? -God!
-把它拔掉  -天哪  好的  你不要动
-Get it! -Jesus! Okay! Just stop!
-安吉  你都干了些什么?  -他就是个毒贩子!
-Angie,What did you do? -He's one of the drug dealers!
-他是我的上家  -他是你的上家?
-He's my pot dealer. -He's your pot dealer?
-我准备拔了  -搞定了
-I got it. -Get it.
-真恶心  你还好吧?  -戴尔  他是谁啊?
-Gross. Are you okay? -Dale,Who is this?
-他是我的糟了  快趴下  -老爸!
-He's my Oh, shit. Get down. -Dad!
什么声音?
What was that?
枪声
That was a gunshot.
住手  住手  快住手!
Stop! stop it! stop it!
-他是我朋友  -我是个好毒贩
-He's with me. -I'm the good drug dealer.
-把枪放下!  -快把枪放下
-Put the gun down! -Put down the gun.
你们两混蛋按我说的做
You assholes do exactly what I say
否则我就把你俩拉到街上去收拾
or I will take you outside and fuck you in the street.
-不  -不要这么对我们
-No don't. -Don't fuck us anywhere.
外面有人吗?
Anybody out there?
跟我们玩捉迷藏
Fucking hide-and-seek.
看这里
Say now.
食物还是热的
Hey,the food's still warm.
太爽了
Love it.
索尔快上来  上来  上来
Come on,saul. come on. come on. come on.
太好了  我们做到了  大家安全了
Yes. we made it. we're all safe guys. we made it.
-你们在干吗  -给我下车
-What are you doing? -Get out.
快下车  你们居然想开我的车走
Get out of my car. I can't believe you think it's an option.
好吧  好吧  听起来有道理  有道理
Okay. okay. That makes sense. It makes sense.
快点  快下车  他说的有道理
Come on, Let's go. It makes sense. He's right.
-离我家人远点  -那我们去哪里?  该怎么做?
-Stay away from my family. Period. -So where do we go? What do we do?
你们去戴斯酒店?
Go to the days inn downtown okay?
用假名登记
Use a fake name.
就用格拉格里这个名字  我会和你联系的
Garagely. I'll contact you.
我不知道那些是什么人  他们会做什么
I don't know who these people are, what they're capable of
但是我发誓会确保你们的安全
but I will keep you guys safe I promise that.
快滚开  混蛋
Fuck off,loser.
安吉  你这个白痴  我满怀爱意说的这句话
Angie,you're a fucking idiot. I say that with love.
我们跟踪了手机信号
We triangulated the cells.
他们砸烂了一个  扔了一个  想妨碍我们的追踪
They smashed one threw the other in the woods to try to distract us.
贾瑞德花了1小时才找到它
It took an hour for jared to find it.
他还找到了丹顿的车
And then he said that he found denton's car
里面有各种奇怪的变装道具
filled with all these strange disguises.
一顶假发 一顶草帽 一件体操服
A powdered wig,a sombrero,leotards.
这他妈的什么意思?
I mean,what the fuck does that mean?
为何不直接打电话给张呢?
Why don't I just call the asians and talk to cheung?
为何不直奔主题呢?
Why beat around the bush you know?
你好?
Hello?
张  我是泰德
Cheung it's ted.
录下我们的对话
Record this conversation.
泰德  真是个惊喜啊  有什么能为你效劳吗?
Ted, what a surprise. what can I do for you?
好吧  张  把话挑明了说
Well cheung my friend,let me tell you.
你昨晚派了一个经验丰富的
You know,we both know that you sent one of your very skilled
打手到这儿来  而我和我同事
hit men over here last night,and I and my colleague
在窗户上做的装饰被他看见了
made a little decoration on our window. should have seen it.
他的脑浆溅到了墙上
We painted the wall with his brain. painted it.
现在这个叫戴尔的家伙?  是动真格的吗?
And now this dale denton guy? you serious?
收手吧  好吗  否则你就是自寻死路  你想吗?
Just stop it,okay? stop it or you're asking for war. do you want a war?
继续吧
Bring it on.
你给我听着  操你妈的!
You listen to me,you motherfucker!
战争开始了!  我们会不惜一切代价的!
It is on! We're coming at you with everything we got!
战争开始了  你最好给我清醒起来
It's on,so you better get your head out of your ass
做好一切准备!
and be ready for everything!
你死定了!
You are fucking dead!
你这个蠢货
You are so dumb.
你让我们弱势尽露?
Do you have any idea how weak you just made us look?
去他妈的!
Goddamn it!
正和我意
Totally sweet.
泰德已经不行了
Ted jones is slipping.
我们现在可以全力攻击了
We shall strike now with full force.
你兄弟不会白死的
Your brother's death will not be in vain.
老实说  我之前接触过很多大麻贩子
I gotta say,I've had,like a lot of weed dealers in my day.
你是最酷的  其他都是混蛋
You're the coolest I've ever had. they were all dicks.
-真的吗?  谢谢  -不客气
-Really? thanks man. -No problem.
我真的很感谢  这对我意义非凡
I really appreciate it. That means a lot to me.
这就像是
It's like
你是我众多买家中唯一一个和我成为朋友的
You're the first guy that I ever sold to that I became friends with.
他们都说公私要分明
They say like "don't dip the pen in company ink."
但是我俩却成了朋友
I'm totally glad I dipped in your ink bro.
是啊
Yeah.
下一步要离开城镇
We should get out of town. that's probably our next move.
坐巴士走  是吗?
Just get on a bus and leave right?
那得先买票
Get bus tickets.
去其他镇  再报警
Go to the next town. contact some police.
你听到我刚才说什么了吗  我说我真的
You know what I was saying? like I'm totally
你很高兴和我成为朋友
You're glad you dipped your pen in my ink.
但是我们得买票坐巴士离开  是不是?
But we should get bus tickets and leave,right?
什么?
What?
坐巴士?  离开这里?  买车票?
Get on the bus? leave? buy bus tickets?
我大概只有50块钱  我觉得买一张票都不够
I only have like 50 bucks. I don't think that'll even buy one ticket.
你那些货呢?
What about your sack?
带着可真受罪  我胆战心惊的
Oh man it's fucking killing me. I feel like I popped one.
你挺倒霉的  但是我不是说这个
No. that's unfortunate but that's not what I'm talking about.
我的意思是你那些小包装的大麻
I mean like the sack of weed.
我们能不能卖一些大麻
Couldn't we just like sell some weed
用那钱买车票?
get some cash and buy bus tickets?
-当然可以  伙计  这就是我的职业  -对啊  太好了
-Of course man. That's what I do. -That's what you do. Fucking a.
你们是不是要买周日比赛的票?
Okay so you're gonna buy tickets for saturday's game,right?
那些队员太棒了
These guys are amazing.
你他妈的想干嘛?
What the fuck do you want?
想不想找点刺激?
You guys wanna buy some chronic?
这玩意儿叫什么来着?
What's this stuff called again?
菠萝快车  他们都说8次了
Pineapple express. they said it eight times.
-是的  但你们别这么叫它  -这不是它的名字
-Yeah,but don't call it that. -Yeah,that's not what it's called.
-就叫它香蕉船吧  -你们可得到此为止
-Call it banana boat. -Make sure you leave it at weed too.
这很容易引人吸毒  但你们别吸毒
This can be a gateway drug. Don't wanna move on to other things.
-比如可卡因  不要尝试  -我们不会乱来的
-Cocaine. Don't do that. -We don't fuck around.
-别瞎操心  别指挥我们  -说话算话啊
-Don't worry. Don't tell us what to do. -Inhale it chachi. Inhale it.
什么话呢?
Who the fuck's chachi?
-你们有多少钱  -快点
-How much money you guys got? -Come on.
你们每人尽可能多得抓一把
You each get as much as you can grab with one hand.
别急  你这把抓了好多
Go easy. That's a big handful guys. come on.
-藏好了  -别告诉别人哪儿来的
-Keep it on the down-low. -Don't tell anybody where you got it.
你是从索尔那里不对  就说是从圣地亚哥还有邓巴那里弄到的
You got it from saul I mean,you got it from santiago and dunbar.
-快走  快点  -快  快  快跑!
-Go. come on. -Go go. vamoose!
你做到了  伙计
You fucking did it man.
你真是个销售天才  你做到了
You are a good salesman. You got it in you man.
我们得去庆祝一下
I'm about to go get some celebratory slushees.
去买些玉米煎饼还是别的什么
Get some burritos or something.
还要买些饮料啊  买些好喝的
Something to drink too. Something good.
一会儿见  伙计
See you man. nice.
不许动  你不要动  这玩意儿杀伤力很大
Don't move. don't you move. this shit hurts.
不许动  你手上拿的是什么?
Don't move. what's in your hand?
是大麻卷烟
It's weed. It's a joint. It's a roach.
-不要动  -我只是在抽烟
-Right here. -I was just smoking
说实话我觉得这并不犯法
I thought it was decriminalized to be honest with you.
我的嗅觉有问题  可以帮我增加食欲  对不起
I have horrible anorexia and it helps my appetite. I'm so sorry.
向学生出售麻醉药品是违法的
Look selling narcotics to my students is not decriminalized.
-好吧  我明白了  -我是警局和学校的联络员
-Okay. I understand. -I'm the liaison officer for this school.
我刚才看到三个学生从这后面走出来
And guess what? I just saw three students walking from back here
眼睛要多红有多红  你这个混蛋
with their eyes as red as the devil's dick. you're busted.
-趴下  趴下  -好吧  好吧
-On the hood. On the hood. -Okay okay.
我已经趴下了呀  你干吗
I'm on the hood. come on.
-站着别动  别动  -我不动  对不起
-Stand still. Stand still. -I'm still. I'm sorry.
你最好祈祷你没有任何犯罪记录
You better hope it's clean. Better hope ain't shit on this record.
信不信我踹你屁股
I'm gonna put my foot up in your ass.
戴眼镜的性感小伙儿
Oh big sexy with glasses.
这里是芭芭拉警官  请求支援逮捕逃犯戴尔·丹顿
This is officer barbara. requesting an update on fugitive dale denton.
重复  请求支援逮捕逃犯戴尔·丹顿
I repeat requesting update on dale denton.
我刚拘捕了他
I have the fugitive in custody.
425  425  告诉我你的位置?
425,425 what's your location?
你给我趴着
You going down.
什么  你什么意思?  为什么我要趴着?
What? What do you mean? Why am I going down?
你查到什么了?  你在干吗?
What did that thing tell you? What are you doing?
我有透露什么吗?  我有透露什么吗?
What did I tell you? What did I tell you?
我什么都没干  你为什么这么讨厌我?
I wasn't doing things. Why do you hate me so much?
交通肇事逃逸  丹顿先生  交通肇事
Hit-and-run,mr. denton. hit-and-run.
2天前  你撞了2辆停着的车
Two parked cars, two nights ago.
其中一辆是警车
One of them was actually a police cruiser.
你是我拘捕过的最蠢的人了
You gotta be the dumbest motherfucker in captivity.
是那个女警  他们抓到戴尔了  糟了
It's the lady cop. They got dale. oh shit.
你是说你看到泰德·琼斯
So you're telling me you saw ted jones
和一个警官射杀了一个人?
and a police officer shoot somebody?
-是的  -你亲眼所见?
-Exactly. -And you saw it?
-是的  你相信我吗  -我不知道  你等等
-Yes,do you believe me? -I don't know.Give me a minute.
-是男的还是女的?  -是个女警  女的
-It was a woman or a man? -It was a policewoman. a woman.
-我想我知道那个贱人是谁  -是的  我也认得那个贱人
-I think I know who that bitch was. -Yes. I will identify that bitch.
谢谢你相信我  女士  谢谢
Thank you so much for believing me ma'am. thank you.
告诉你  我会查清整件事的真相
I'll tell you,I'll get to the bottom of it.
我会抛开我的身份去查清它的
I'll take this badge off,get to the bottom of it.
我不为法律效力  是法律在为我效力
I don't work for the law. The law works for me.
我觉得事情有些蹊跷
I been smelling something in this department.
你注意看路啊
Keep your eyes on the road.
-我肯定会调查清楚的  -停车
-Gonna get to the bottom of this shit. -Stop!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
不是吧  到底怎么了  那是什么东西?
Oh no. What the hell was that? What is that?
不是吧  不是吧  不是吧
No,no,no.
-你要干什么?  -我在救你啊!
-No. what are you doing? -I'm saving you, amigo!
不许动  别想从我这里过!
Freeze goddamn it! Don't even think about it!
这真是个过时的逃脱任务啊  伙计
This is an old-fashioned escape mission, buddy.
快停车!
Stop this car!
-你他妈的到底在干吗?  -糟了!  糟了!
-What the fuck are you doing? -Oh shit! oh shit!
糟了!
Oh shit!
死定了  是那个女警  那个凶手!  快开车!
Oh shit! it's the lady cop! That's the murderer! go!
-那个是女警  -那个是谁?
-That's the lady cop. -Who's that?
我不知道  她们开枪了!
I don't know. They're shooting!
我的天呐  她们在朝我们开枪!
Oh my god,they're shooting!
操
Fuck.
伙计当心啊!
Dude!
我看不见路!  玻璃上都是饮料!
I can't see! the slushee!
-开雨刮器!  -它失灵了!
-Turn on the wipers! -It's not working!
好吧  那就把挡风玻璃踢开!
Well kick out the window!
-用一条腿怎么开车啊?  -我也不知道!
-How do you drive with one foot? -I don't know!
操!  我伤到命根子了!
Fuck! I think I pulled my groin!
把腿弄出来啊
Get your foot out of there.
她就在我们后面
She's gaining on us. She's behind us.
她车开得比较好啊
Her car's better.
-你得把腿先弄出来  我说真的  -可我拔不出啊
-Get your leg out of there. Seriously. -I can't.
尽你所能把车开最快啊!
Put it into maximum overdrive!
要啊  不要啊  不要啊!
Oh,no,no,no!
一团糟!
Oh,shit!
快把它拔出来!
Get it out!
我看不见路啊!
I can't see!
小心!  小心!  当心树!  树!  树!  还有松鼠!
Danger! danger! trees! tree! tree! squirrel!
你看  我能从这个腿插出来的洞里看路
Hey,I can see through my leg hole.
好吧!  小心!  有树!  树!  树!
Nice! look out! tree! tree! tree!
你甩掉她了  伙计
You did it man.
好吧!  当心!
All right! look out!
天哪!
Oh shit!
调头!  调头!
Turn around! turn around!
我好害怕  索尔  我好怕
I'm scared saul. I'm scared.
-别急  我来搞定  -那你快啊
-Don't worry. I'm handling this. -Do something.
好吧  你抓紧了  我有个主意
All right, hold on. I got an idea.
什么狗屁主意  快开车  快开车
Oh shit! oh shit! go! go! go! go!
不好意思啊
Sorry!
你刚才想干吗?
What the fuck was that?
操  不好意思啊  我以为她会开过头的
Fuck. I'm sorry. I thought she'd just go past.
-为啥?  -我也不知道
-Why? -I don't know.
天哪
Oh,my.
太棒了!  我们做到了!  我们做到了!  伙计
Yes! yes! we made it! all right man.
-那我们快逃吧  -不是吧  你在干嘛?
-Let's get the fuck out of here. -No. what are you doing?
你个白痴  我还在车上呢  快回来!
You forgot me you idiot! come back!
快回来!  索尔!
Come back! saul!
-对不起啊  伙计  -谢了
-Sorry man. -Thank you.
-快跑  -等等  拿手铐钥匙  你这个白痴
-Let's go. -Wait. Get the handcuff keys, you idiot.
泰德  我们一干掉那些坏蛋
As soon as we kill those sacks of shit tonight ted
就继续新生活
I'm moving on.
好的
Okay.
好吧
All right.
而且我保证你会没事的
And I promise you you're gonna be taken care of.
那是当然的
As sure as shit you will.
我计划如下
For now this is what we're gonna do.
我们今晚就去农场  搬一些货
We're gonna go to the farm tonight, we're gonna move tonight's shipment.
明天一早  去干掉那些家伙
Then tomorrow morning we're gonna hunt these guys down.
戴尔  索尔  还有那些亚洲人  赶尽杀绝
Dale saul the asians. every last one of them.
他们全部都得死
We're gonna fucking kill them all.
那你给我笑一个
So smile.
闭嘴
Shut up.
说两句西班牙语来听听  说吧  说吧
Say something in spanish. go ahead. I dare you. go ahead.
你接受安全监听了吗?
All right. are you using protection?
-这里是戴斯酒店  -好的
-Days inn. -Yes.
麻烦帮我接格拉格里的房间?
May I have the garagely room please?
-你好  -你好  这里是安吉?
-Hello? -Hello is angie there?
-戴尔  -是安吉吗?
-Dale. -Angie?
-天哪  你还好吧?  -我很好啊  好得不得了
-My god are you okay? -I'm good. I'm fine. I'm great.
-你呢  -我很好啊
-Are you okay? -Yes,I'm fine.
那就好  我想到了一个计划
Okay good. I came up with a plan.
可能初听起来有点怪  但是你只需要先听着
It might sound weird at first but just listen.
戴尔  你知道吗  你惹火了毒贩  我来告诉你
Dale. you know what? drug dealers Let me tell you something.
毒贩正在追杀我  还有你  还有我的家人
Drug dealers are trying to kill me. and you. and my family.
我会落入如此田地  就是因为你
I can't believe I'm in this situation right now because of you
还有你的毒瘾  难以置信  我居然要逃命
and your addiction to marijuana. I cannot believe I'm here.
第一  我没对大麻上瘾
I can't be addicted to marijuana.
我用东西过滤了致瘾成分的  我说真的
A, I use a bong. it filters out the addictive shit. seriously.
第二  就算我吸大麻又有什么关系 我是那场谋杀案的目击者
B, what does that have to do with anything? I witnessed murder.
而我现在正在处理这一切
And now I'm dealing with it.
我们之间发生的一切是很正常的啊
This that's happening between us this is normal.
那些交往过三个月的情侣  哪个不会碰上这事呢
This happens to every couple dating for three months.
-我们应该一起渡过难关  -才不是
-We have to work through it. -No.
这样倒霉事可不是谁都能撞上
This doesn't happen to anyone.
我本不该陷入如此境地  全都怪你
I should not be in this situation, so fuck you.
知道吗  我们完了
You know what? it's over.
好吧  很好  随便你了  我们完了
Good. fine. whatever. it's over.
恭喜了  注定发生的事情?  现在发生未尝不可?
Congratulations. had to happen sometime,right? why not now?
他妈的  那是什么意思?
What the fuck does that mean?
这就是说  你明年就上大学了
It means that you are gonna go to college next year.
你会就此沉迷"黑暗帝王风驰电掣"
You'll get into godspeed you! black emperor
还有该死的"胫骨乐队"
and the fucking shins.
你会排斥身边的俊男们  最后变成一个女同志
And you'll blow a bunch of dudes and become a lesbian
而我  还在该死的克拉克郡应付这些烂摊子
and I'll be here in fucking clark county doing shit-all.
你要甩了我  去他妈的  玩得开心吧
You're gonna dump me. so, fuck it, have a good time.
女同志  你就是个混蛋  戴尔!
A lesbian? fuck you, dale!
反正你根本不喜欢我  是吧?
You never did like me anyway, did you?
你根本不想见我父母
You didn't wanna meet my parents.
我一直很在乎你  但这是两回事?
I always cared about you. that's not what this is ever. okay?
我永远在乎你
I always care about you.
那你为什么言行不一呢?
Why don't you ever act like it, huh?
为什么你的所作所为不是那么回事?
Why do you never act like you care about anything?
我他妈的吸多了大麻!
Because I'm high! fuck! and it
你想怎么样?  算了  上帝啊
What do you want? okay. jesus.
我能回家的时候  电话通知我
Call me when I can go home.
你打牌的时候输光了?  你这个混蛋
You lost it playing bid whist? you pimp.
好的  我可以再给你点钱
No,I'll give you more
但是你不能用来赌博
But you cannot gamble with it.
我知道  那些表的事情很遗憾
I know, I'm sorry about the clocks.
我想不起来是今天还是明天
I couldn't remember if it was today or tomorrow.
好了  我得挂了
All right,I gotta go.
我爱你
I love you.
你个机灵鬼
You wise-ass.
老兄  你没事吧?  手忙脚乱的
Hey,you all right,man? That sounded pretty hectic.
没事  我们快离开这个鬼地方吧
I'm okay. let's just get the fuck out of here.
要事第一
First things first.
-别吸了  好不好?  -为什么不呢?
-don't do that okay? -yeah. why not?
还问为什么?  飞车追踪  枪林弹雨
Why not? car chase, gunshots.
应该是刚才的事情吧
That clearly just happened
就因为我们吸食了大麻
because we were smoking marijuana.
不对  之所以发生那些事
No man. it happened because those kids
是因为那些孩子不懂隐藏
couldn't keep their shit on the down-low.
如果你意识不到你该留意的事情
In case you haven't noticed which you haven't.
我敢说你从来没在意过任何事情
From what I can tell you don't notice anything ever.
我们吸大了的时候  从来没清醒过
We are not very functional when we're high.
没他妈清醒过
Which is all the fucking the time.
我不太清楚  但是现在我很清醒
Well,I don't know man.I think I'm functioning right now.
把你从条子那里救出来的时候
I was like stoned
就醉醺醺的
When I saved you with those slushees.
那又怎么呢?
What do you gotta say to that?
好吧  如果你真救了  我就承认
Well that would be true if you had saved me.
但是你根本没救着我
But you didn't save me.
她要帮忙  你却跟着添乱
She was gonna help,you made things worse.
我们被一群疯子追杀
We're wanted for all sorts of crazy shit.
别他妈往我身上扯  行吗?
Don't fucking get on my case,all right?
我之所以进行大麻交易
Look,Only reason I started selling pot
是为了送我奶奶去好的养老院
is so I could put my bubbe in a nice retirement home.
-因为这个  她一定为你骄傲  -她真的为我骄傲
-she must be proud of you for that. -she is really proud of me.
我会一举成名的
I'm gonna become something.
等她去世之后  我打算做一个土木工程师
As soon as she dies,I'm gonna become a civil engineer.
我要给游乐场设计化粪池
I'm gonna design septic tanks for playgrounds.
小孩子也能在那儿拉屎
Little kids can take shits.
你个白痴  你究竟能做什么?
You idiot. what the hell do you do?
我能做什么  要不是拜你所赐
What am I gonna do? besides stay in my home
除了待在家里不敢出门?
for fear that you've designed some object I'm around?
我会在电台节目里讨论人生
I'm gonna be on the radio talking about life.
-关于人生的经验之谈  -看看我的理想
-giving lessons about life. -put me in my place.
我要设计建筑  看看他做什么
I'm gonna be designing buildings and what's he doing?
无聊要死的人在电台做节目
Boring people to death on the radio.
你就是个混蛋  根本就是个混蛋
You are an asshole. that's all you are. you're an asshole.
-我不是混蛋  -你就是
-I'm not an asshole. -you are an asshole.
我肯定不是混蛋
I feel pretty sure that I'm not an asshole.
我是个十足的好人
I'm like a totally nice guy.
我跟你一样好  别拿那个说事
I'm just as nice as you are. so don't bring that out.
在树林里的时候  我把夹克衫给了你
We were in the woods.I gave you my jacket.
给你雪中送炭
You were cold and I clothed you.
那在公园的时候是怎么回事
How about in the park
我说把你当朋友?
When I said that you were my friend?
你没做任何回应
You didn't say anything back.
那很明显  因为我们根本不是朋友
Well that's easy. it's because we're not friends.
我从你那儿买毒品
You are my drug dealer.
这是我们认识的唯一原因
There's one reason we know each other.
我喜欢你的毒品  就这么简单
I like the drugs you sell. that's it.
如果你不卖毒品  我根本不会认识你
If you didn't sell those drugs, I would have no idea who you were
我现在会逍遥自在  而不是如此狼狈不堪
and I would be fantastic right now. instead of looking like this.
这话太残忍了  太冷血无情了
That sounded mean. just hearing it sounded mean.
-我不该说出来的  -你说了
-I didn't mean to say -it's out.
老兄  水都泼出去了
Monkey's out of the bottle,man.
什么  那根本就不是话
What? that's not even an expression.
覆水难收了
Pandora doesn't go back in the box. he only comes out.
老兄  对不起
I'm sorry, man. look
-你干什么呢  -给你  好好吃最后一顿饭
-what are you doing? -here. have a nice last meal.
老兄  别这样
Come on man. don't do that.
混蛋  为什么不赶快去吃个巨无霸
Why don't you supersize it, bitch?
对不起  老兄  回来
I'm sorry man. look come back.
我不是有意的
I didn't mean that.
我爱你  你爱我吗?
I love you. do you love me?
看起来真棒
That looks great.
喂?
Hello?
戴尔吗?
Dale?
是我
It is dale.
安吉  我打电话给你  就想让你知道
Angie I'm calling
你是我的挚爱
Because I love you more than anything in the world
我愿为你做任何事情
and I wanna let you know I'll do anything to make it work.
任何事情
I'll do anything.
在我命悬一线的时候
I've had a near-death experience and when that happens
你能不顾自己的安危  你就是我的另一半?
you can prioritize your life and you are it, okay?
所以  求你别不要我
So please just take me back please.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
-I love you. -I love you.
-真的吗  -我只怕失去你  戴尔
-yeah? -I just don't wanna lose you, dale.
我们离开房子的时候  就一直在想
We were driving away from the house and I just kept thinking
我也不知道  我就是
I don't know. I just
我想嫁给你
I wanna marry you.
我犯了一个错
I made a mistake.
-你说什么  -我
-what do you mean? -I've
-什么?  -还有一点儿没说完
-what? -I'm just processing that last bit.
-你想要结婚  他妈的 -什么?
-you wanna oh, fuck. -what?
我不知道
I don't know.
如果你到现在还要我
I realize now that if you would take me back
那也太天真幼稚了
then you are very naive and immature.
你不知道我有多混蛋  不配跟任何人交往
You don't see what a fuck-up I am. I'm in no shape to be dated by anyone.
-你才是那么不成熟的人  -我很成熟  你不成熟
-you're the one that's immature. -I'm not immature. you're immature.
我承认我是有点不成熟
I am somewhat immature
但是你更幼稚  我要比你还大一些呢
But you're more immature. I'm older.
就因为你大我几岁
Just because you're older.
我14岁的时候就不是处女之身了
I lost my virginity when I was 14 years old.
-真的吗  -你跟多少女孩上过床
-really? -how many girls have you slept with?
-大概2个半  -2个半?
-like, two and a half. -two and a half?
那半个是什么?  手淫吗?  那不算数
What is a half? your hand?That doesn't count
不  我只进去了一半  我想不起来为什么了
No it was the tip or I dipped a ball in. I can't remember why.
我就记得我想  这不算一次
I remember thinking "this doesn't count as a full point."
如果我说3个女孩,那我是在撒谎
If I said three I'd feel like a liar.
我当时烂醉如泥
I don't know why,I was drunk.
去你的
Screw you.
赶快让我离开这个鬼地方
Get me out of this motel room.
我会的  是我能给的最后一个承诺了?
I will and that's the last you'll ever hear from me, okay?
谢天谢地
Oh thank goodness. okay.
宝格斯  菲亚·宝格斯
Belogus. Faye Belogus.
瞧瞧  瞧瞧
Look at there. look at there.
你用那个泳池吗?
Do you use the pool over here?
是的  你们到底要我做什么?
Yes I use the pool. come on what do you want from me?
你孙子  你给他打电话
Your grandson. we need you to get on the phone with your grandson
你们说什么呢关我孙子什么事?
What are you talking about my grandson?
你们告诉我要坐在这儿跟我玩多米诺骨牌
You told me you wanna sit down play dominos with me.
现在跟我说什么我的孙子
And now you're hocking me about my grandson.
不知道你们说什么  不知所云
Is that yiddish? yes. yes it is.
可以叫你菲亚吗?
May I call you faye?
你可以叫我菲亚  但是我要叫你死鬼
You can call me faye but I'm gonna call you a stinker.
你好  曼得森夫人
Hey Mrs. Mendelson.
你又想要什么?
What do you want from me?
奶奶,你们好
Bubbe. hey guys.
-看谁送上门来了  -你好  宝贝儿
-well look who it is. -hello baby.
该死
Damn.
妈的
Oh shit.
抱歉  贝蒂
Sorry, Betty.
他们绑架了我的孙子
They kidnapped my grandson.
没错  那2个人进来
Yeah these two guys came in
坐在我旁边  要跟我玩多米诺骨牌
they sat down with me to play dominos.
我不认识他们
I never saw them in my life before.
他们一直问我孙子的事情
And they kept asking questions about my grandson.
-他们长什么样? -一个很高  穿着很邋遢
-what did they look like? -one of them was very tall and sloppy.
另外一个  样子很帅
And the other guy he was very good-looking
但是个十足的小矮人
but he was short as shit.
最糟的是
But the worst part was
这时候  我孙子走进来  穿着睡衣裤
that my grandson came in why and in pajamas.
-一定要找到我的孙子  -我们会尽力的
-you gotta find my grandson. -We'll do the best
-你能保证吗?  -我保证
-do you promise? -I promise.
一定要  你脸上有点东西
Absolutely. you've got something there.
那是个痣  夫人
I believe that's a mole ma'am.
你个混蛋  捅了多大的篓子?
You sack of shit. do you know what a pain in the ass you've been?
不  老兄  我不想出去
No man. I don't wanna get out.
谁给你的棒棒糖?  走
Who gave you that lollipop? let's go.
这是什么地方?  什么?
Where am i man? what?
你们的人先挑衅的  我根本不想来这里
You guys started it man. I don't even wanna be here.
糟糕  那是我干的吗?
Shit. did I do that?
算了
Hey hey. all right, okay.
混蛋!
Fuck you,man!
-退后  -什么?  -泰德想留活口  -为什么拦着我?
-stand back.-What? -Ted wants him alive. -why you holding me back?
泰德要留活口?
Ted wants him alive okay?
我要踢掉他几颗牙
I should be kicking his fucking teeth in.
如果有人该揍他的话  那也该是泰德
If anybody's gonna beat him, it's ted.
我看起来像汉堡神偷
I look like hamburglar.
还是一个象人
And the elephant man.
看来某人被咖啡壶给干了
Like someone fucked you up with a coffee pot.
专业点  专业点
Professional. professional.
-这种时候专业  -随你怎么说了
-professional on this, bitch. -whatever, man.
-你当时在哪儿  -我在那儿
-where were you? -I was there.
-你本该帮我的  -我在那儿
-supposed to be my partner. -I was there.
不  如果你在那儿  我的脸怎么会这样?
No you wasn't there. how did this happen?
我挨揍了?  就该我倒霉吗?
I take the hit? that's how it's gonna be?
去你的吧?  把他拉出去
Fuck all this you know? get him out of here.
带他下楼去  让这混蛋滚出我的视线
Take him downstairs. get this asshole out of my sight.
我要离这个家伙远点
I don't wanna go near this guy.
下面是什么?  陷阱?
What's down there? fucking rancor?
我会动粗的
I might act tough
但是我感觉
but I got a lot of feelings.
你伤害了他们所有人
And you hurt damn near every one of them.
这事儿没完
This ain't over.
-你知道你要死了  是吧?  -是
-you know you gonna die, right? -yeah.
我会宰了你
I'm gonna kill the fuck out of you.
慢慢享受你最后的17分钟吧
I hope you enjoy these last 17 minutes of your life
一旦泰德到了
because when ted gets here
命令杀了你  我就立刻宰了你这个混蛋
"kill that motherfucker." I'm gonna kill your motherfucking ass.
小心头
Watch your head.
看着他
Hey watch him.
天哪  上帝
Oh my god.
黄金宝藏
El dorado.
传说都是真的
The legends are true.
看看这些植株
Look at all this weed, man.
那是什么  紫色祖父?
What's that? purple granddaddy?
-快点  -紫色奶头?
-come on. -purple nurple?
库什
Og kush?
Og kush.
这是我见过最美的东西了
It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
-怎么灌溉  -闭嘴
-what kind of irrigation? -shut up.
-我能摸一下吗?  -过来
-can I touch it? -come here.
有人吗?
Hello?
瑞德?
Red?
-瑞德?  -怎么回事?
-red? -what the fuck?
出去  丹顿  我不干了
Get out of here man. I didn't do shit denton.
我为了和解而来  我不是来跟你打架的
Look,I come in peace okay? I'm not here to fight you again.
很好
Good.
我太累了  内心燥热不堪
Because I'm tired man. I'm feeling so hot.
你看起来很糟
You don't look great.
他们射中了我  丹顿
They shot me,denton.
正好射中这里了
They got me right here.
-是吗  -就是这儿
-yeah? -right here.
然后他们又射中了这儿
And then they got me again right here.
老兄  我现在打911
Look man I'll call 911 right now.
他们会救你的?
They'll save your life okay?
-你没有必要死  -不
-you don't need to die. -no bro.
你还没懂  无论我在哪里
You don't get it. it doesn't really matter where I'm at.
不管我是在医院  还是在这儿
If I'm at the hospital, if I'm here
泰德都能找到我的
ted's gonna find me man. he will.
他一旦找到我  我必死无疑了
And when he does he's gonna fucking kill me.
他就是个混蛋
He's just like an asshole.
瑞德  你说的没错  我就是为这个来的?
I couldn't agree more red. that's why I've come here okay?
你知道泰德?  他绑走了索尔
You know ted? he took saul.
我要救他
And I'm gonna get him back.
就像他救我那样
You know like he saved my life.
我们共患难  他是个可靠的朋友  一个好人
We've been on the run together. he's a great friend. a good guy.
没错  索尔是个好人
He is. I'll tell you that man. saul is a good dude.
我对他太苛刻了
I was mean to him man.
我误解他了  我不能让事情就这么结束
I wronged him and I can't I can't let it end like that.
我转信佛教了  我现在以平常心接受事实
I'm just into buddhism and I'm at peace with the fact
我要丢下这个臭皮囊
that me as this person, probably gonna not be around.
跟寄居蟹一样?
Think about a hermit crab okay?
人的灵魂就是从一个外壳转移到另外一个
And it's a shell and it's like they go from one shell to the next.
就跟我现在一样  就是一个寄居蟹换了个壳
And that's what I am. it's like I'm just a hermit crab changing shells.
如果你这辈子窝囊
Except if you're a dick your whole life
下辈子也不会好到哪去?
your next shell will be made of shit, okay?
这辈子你是个混蛋  转世你可能就是个蟑螂
If you're an asshole you're gonna come back as a cockroach.
或者是一只虫子  或者一泡屎?
Or a worm or a fucking anal bead okay?
如果你是个男子汉  英勇无畏
If you're a man and you act heroic
你下辈子可能转世为一只雄鹰  翱翔天际
you'll come back as an eagle.
或者下辈子蛟龙得水
You'll come back as a dragon.
又或是裘·洛德转世
You'll come back as jude law.
自己想想吧?  自己想要成为什么?
Okay? which would you rather be?
也许是那泡屎  要看是谁拉的了
Maybe the anal bead. might depending on who it belongs to.
我拉的
It belongs to me.
-我要蛟龙得水  -这才像话
-then the dragon. -exactly.
你得帮我  化疼痛为力量
You need to help me okay? just use it you know? use the pain.
你能雄风再起
You'll have a second wind.
振作起来  我们去救索尔吧
Let's get up and go get saul back. use it.
-你不恨泰德吗?  -我恨透他了
-aren't you angry at ted? -yeah I'm really mad at him.
那你不想起来了?  做点什么吗?
What do you wanna do? don't you wanna get up do something about it?
能干掉他  也许会很酷
Maybe that would be cool to do to him.
我们的答案不是也许
I don't think "maybe" is the answer.
我认为你该说"戴尔  我会帮你"
I think,"yes I'm gonna help you, dale"
这才是我想要的答案
that's the answer I'm looking for.
过来
Come here.
泰德·琼斯同瓜农闹翻了
Ted jones messed with the wrong melon farmers.
暴力人生
Thug life.
该死
Oh shit.
捡起来  我可不想它被吸尘器吸进去
Get those. I don't wanna run them over in the vacuum cleaner
-然后爆了我的头  -对不起
-and shoot my face off, okay? -I'm sorry.
我以前当男妓的时候  用过这种小枪
I used to use this little gun when I was a prostitute.
别动
Don't.
举起手来
差不多就是那么快了
Just something quick like that.
-不许动  -没错
-don't. -yeah.
-不许动  立刻住手  -住手
-don't. you stop it right now. -stop it.
天哪
Oh god.
真是一个大窝点啊
That's a big hideout.
我做不来  对不起  我做不来
I can't do this. I'm sorry. I can't do this.
我伤口感染  我需要治疗
I'm infected. my shit's all fucked up. I need medical attention.
做不来了什么意思?
What you mean you can't?
刚刚还热血沸腾  现在这是怎么了?
I thought we just got all pumped up. what was that about?
泰德是个杀人不眨眼的凶手  我斗不过他
Ted is a fucking murderer. I can't fuck with him.
我还有妻子  不久之后就出狱了
I got a wife. she's gonna be out of jail soon.
我还要跟她做爱
I wanna fuck her.I wanna to have sex with her.
我还想见到明天的太阳
I am not gonna wake up murdered tomorrow.
老兄  这就让你裹足不前了吗
Oh man no. this is lame of you man.
是你赎罪的时候了
Come on. this could be your moment of redemption.
这一刻属于你
This could be your moment.
-我不要这样的时刻  不要  -算了  走吧
-I don't want a moment. I don't want -Fine, go.
滚你的吧
Fuck you.
拜托回来帮帮我吧  回来吧
Please come back for me. please come back.
传奇将永恒  你会流芳百世的
Legends never die dude. I'll tell your story.
卡罗尔  她现在好多了
Carol, she's cool now.
她以前真的太疯了
Carol used to be a little crazy man.
沉迷于聚会
She used to throw tickle parties.
-听起来像过家家  -那很有趣
-sounds like home-cooking to me. -that was fun.
游戏结束了  混球们!  都不许动
Game over motherfuckers! everybody freeze!
告诉我我朋友在哪  要不就崩了他!
Tell me where my friend is or this guy gets it!
好的  大家别动  别乱来
All right everybody be cool man. be cool.
放下枪  我们就不会开枪
Put your guns down. nobody shoots.
把枪放到地上
Put them down. on the ground.
好吧  看谁更狠
All right everybody just chill.
天哪!
Oh my god!
-你射中他了  -放下枪
-you shot him. -put the gun down.
-把枪放下  -别射我!
-drop the fucking gun. -don't shoot me!
-见鬼  -我说了没人会开枪  你射中了皮特
-holy shit. -I said nobody shoot. you shot pete.
没错  我射中他了  射中了
That's right. I shot him. I shot him.
我打他了  我没时间他妈的跟他们讨价还价
I shot him. I don't have time for a fucking negotiation.
我想事情赶快了结  我就能回家了
Now I wanna finish this off so I can go home
跟我妻子共进一次晚餐
and have dinner with my wife for once.
有谁问起  就说是丹顿杀了皮特
If anybody asks denton killed pete.
别编故事了
End of story.
我会告诉泰德
I'm telling ted.
-如果你告密的话  -他还有一支
-lf you do -he's got a piece.
-混蛋  -好了  我错了
-motherfucker. -okay I'm sorry.
里面还藏了一把
He's got another one right inside.
该死  我裤腿里还有一把
Damn it. I got one more on my leg.
还有一把  我知道你们总能找到  给你
There's one more. I know you'll find it. take it.
抱歉  对不起骗了你们
I'm sorry guys. sorry I deceived you.
别这样
No. come on.
-太戏剧了  -索尔
-oh great. -saul.
-戴尔  -是
-dale. -yes.
你出卖我了?  这就是你干的  混蛋?
What did you do rat me out? is that what you did you bastard?
-没有  -你有
-no man. -yes.
我是来救你的
I'm here to save you.
不  你凑巧也被逮住了
No. you just got caught too.
我就要和某个混蛋死在这儿了
And I'm gonna die in here with some asshole.
好吧  你知道吗?  我活该这样
Okay you know what? I deserved that.
我活该是因为我曾经是个混蛋
I'll take that because I have been an asshole man.
整件事都是我的错  我毁了你的生活
This whole thing is my fault. I ruined your life.
我知道没什么能够补偿你的
Okay? and I know there's no way
除非救你出去
to make that up to you except by saving your life.
这就是我为什么来  来救我最好的朋友
So that's what I came here to do. I'm here to save my best friend.
因为你就是我最好的朋友
Because that's what you are. you're my best friend.
你这个苛刻的白痴
You're a mean jerk.
我是太苛刻了  是因为
I was mean. I was mean because I think
我不想把你当作我的好朋友
I didn't want you to be my best friend.
我不想面对生活
I didn't wanna think that that's what my life was.
现在我明白了  有友如此  今生难得啊
Now I realize I'm lucky to have you as my best friend.
你是我遇过最好的人了
You're the best guy I know.
我们永远都是好朋友
Bfff.
难兄难弟  一生好友啊  说真的
Best fucking friends forever, man. seriously.
-好了  给我一个拥抱  -好  好
-all right. give me a hug. -yeah. okay.
谢了  老友  过去的事情真的很抱歉
Thanks, man. I'm so sorry about everything.
我就是个混蛋
Oh, I'm such a dick.
-好了  我会让咱脱身的  -不  你不是  但也还好
-okay. I'm gonna get us out. -no, you're not, but it's okay.
这些混球要杀我们  得赶紧出去
These guys are gonna fucking kill us. we gotta get out of here.
-我知道他们想干嘛  -操他的
-I know. they are. -fuck, man.
我们在外边都能听到你吵  声音真他妈大
We can hear you outside and it's very fucking annoying, all right?
-好啦  对不起咯  先生  -闭上鸟嘴
-okay. sorry about that, sir. -shut the fuck up.
你知道"闭上鸟嘴"是什么意思吗?
Do you know what "shut the fuck up" mean?
我知道
I do.
屌  操他奶奶的蠢货
Shit. stupid motherfuckers.
好  好  我有办法了  我的皮带扣  我的皮带扣
Yes. okay. I got an idea. I got an idea. my belt buckle. my belt buckle.
这里  看到不  用你的腰摩擦我的皮带扣  可以的
Right here. okay? rub your wrists against my belt buckle. that'll do it.
-行不?  -我感觉不到
-is it working? -I can't feel it.
我没感觉
I can't feel you.
-等等  有感觉了  -有感觉了  对  好
-wait, I feel it. -I feel it. yes, okay.
-好了  -没错  好
-okay. -okay. okay.
-我会救你的  兄弟  -好  好
-I'm gonna save you, man. -yeah. yeah.
-让我救你  -救我
-let me save you. -save me, Dale.
这样不行  我们要换个角度
It's not working. we gotta change angles.
我们要用Y式,来
We gotta get more leverage-y. okay.
这太好了  这样好
Okay, that's good. that's good.
把你的手放上来  来吧
Get your hands up on it. there we go.
-好啊  好啊  -很好  来
-all right. all right. -yeah. okay.
-好  好  -行了
-yes. yes. -okay.
我要救你  兄弟  我要救你了
I'm gonna save you, man. I'm gonna save you.
-你是最好的朋友  -是吧  来?
-you're my best friend, man. -yeah, see?
-不行啊  -让我用用嘴来
-it's not working. -let me use my I'll use my mouth.
我用嘴干掉它  来吧
Finish it off with my mouth, pal. let's go.
来啊  开始吧
Come on. let's go.
再用力一点
Harder.
-那些混蛋在哪儿啊?  -我们把他们关在楼下
-where are these fuckers? -we got them downstairs.
-你们在哪里找到他们的?  -在索尔奶奶那里找到的
-where did you find them? -found saul at his grandmother's.
他毁了曼德尔森的脸  滚烫的咖啡倒在他的脸上
He fucked up matheson's face. hit him with a pot of hot coffee.
恶心极了
It's gross.
戴尔·丹顿像个傻子一样闯进来
Dale denton comes flying in here like a madman
和我们干架  他杀了皮特
armed to the teeth, and, as you can see, he shot peter.
对他拳脚相加
Plugged him, just whacked him.
现在他们都被绑起来关在楼下
Now they're both disarmed and they're downstairs.
他把皮特给杀了?
He shot pete?
那该死的皮特?  以前可是在国家安全局干的
Fucking pete? he was ex-cia.
戴尔·丹顿他妈的是谁啊?
Who the fuck is this dale denton?
他是什么人?  从哪儿来?  我都不知道
Who is he? where did he come from? I do not know.
是时候去大干一番啦
Time to cook shit up tonight.
带上他的珍藏  把这里炸得底朝天
Take his stash and burn this motherfucker down.
停  等一会儿
Stop. wait here.
不退缩  不投降
No retreat, no surrender.
好极了  好极了  好极了
Yes, yes, yes.
-等下  有人来了  -好  好  好
-wait, someone's coming. -okay, okay, okay.
如果我咳一次那就我先动  如果咳两次就你先动  明白了吗?
If I cough once, I'll take the lead. if I cough twice, you go, okay?
当然了  有时候我是真的在咳嗽
Well I cough sometimes for real.
那就不要  不要
Just don't. don't
你们听着  我就说一次
Yo, look. I'm gonna say this one time.
你们想干嘛我都知道  明白了吗?
Whatever you're doing, I get it, okay?
停下
Stop.
看来你们没有听懂我说的话
See, I don't think you understood me.
你们说的话我都听得到
I can hear everything you're saying.
咳一次是你动  咳两次是你先动
One cough mean you go. two cough mean you take the lead.
那个皮带扣  永远是最好的朋友
The belt buckle. best friends forever.
你们是在浪费时间  伙计
Y'all fuck on your own time, man.
对不起  伙计  这是个愚蠢的计划
Sorry, man. it was a stupid plan.
那他妈是什么?
What the fuck is that?
戴尔!
Dale!
我等这一刻很久了  你烫伤了我的脸!
I've been waiting for this. you burned my face!
我要让你眼泪横飞
I'm gonna tear this ass up.
你向我开枪
You shot me.
伙计  对不起
I'm sorry, man.
我从来都没有被打中过  妈的  好痛啊
I've never been shot. damn, that hurt.
我坐在玻璃渣子上面了
I got glass in my ass.
-戴尔  戴尔!  -这下搞砸了
-dale. dale! -this is messed up.
有人见我的大刀?
Has anyone seen my bigger knife?
亚洲人!
Asians!
你死定了!
War is upon you!
准备承受这该死的因果报应吧!
Prepare to suck the cock of karma!
下来啊  混蛋!
Get down, motherfucker!
上啊!
Come on!
妈的!
Fuck!
走!  走!
Go! go!
宝贝  快蹲下!
Get down, baby!
不  戴尔!
Dale, no!
不  兄弟  快醒过来
No, wake up, man.
不  你还没死呢  兄弟
No, you're not dying, man.
不要丢下我
Not without me.
-戴尔  -怎么了?
-dale. -what?
你还活着
You're alive.
-你你还活着  -发生什么事了?
-you're you're alive. -what happened?
-他打中你的耳朵了  伙计  -他打中我什么了?
-he got your ear, man. -he got my what?
-他打中你的耳朵了  -妈的!
-he got your ear. -fuck!
他妈的!
Fuck!
-救命啊!  -我的耳朵
-help! -my ear.
-好痛啊  -救命啊!
-yeah. -help!
-你打掉了我的耳朵  -你射中我了
-you killed my ear. -you shot me.
-我可没有  -他射中我了
-I didn't do that. -he shot me.
你射中他了?
You shot him?
-别碰我  -给我闭嘴
-get your hands off of me. -shut up.
我们受够你了
We've had enough out of you.
我又不是你的朋友
I'm not your friend.
可能我可以
Maybe I can just
不  不行  会感染的
No. no, infected.
那就这样了吗?  可能只要摁在那里
Is that it? maybe if we just hold it.
我们安全了
It's clear.
伙计  看那儿
Dude. look.
漂亮
Nice.
子弹
Bullets.
说实话  我耳朵有多糟?
So seriously, how gross does my ear look?
是很恶心  还是有点酷?
Is it really disgusting or is it, like, kind of cool in a way?
现在看上去有点恶心
Right now it's pretty disgusting.
我好像能闻到
I feel like I can smell it.
不要担心  兄弟  想想艾万达·何力飞
Don't worry, bro. think about evander holyfield.
你根本没法说
You can't even tell.
说得好
That's a good point.
等等
Wait.
你真的打中了那个人吗?
Did you shoot that guy?
不  我没子弹了
No. I'm out of bullets.
我也没有了
Me too.
可能是跳弹吧
Maybe it was ricochet.
地心引力
Gravity.
太棒了
Oh, nice.
你下去
You go down.
我掩护
I'll cover.
掩护我  我下去解决这一切
Watch my back. I'll go down and take care of this.
真他妈性感
Sexy motherfucker.
不  不  上面可能有更多坏蛋
No, no, there might be more bad guys up there.
不  我们可以从通风口溜出去  快跟上
No, we'll sneak out through the vent. come on.
我先托你上去  然后你再拉我上去
I'll boost you up, okay? and then you pull me up.
好的
Oh, nice.
就是这样  对了
Here we go. okay.
上去  是这样  漂亮
Get up. yeah. nice.
做得好
Nice.
漂亮,好的
Nice. okay.
把我拉上去
Pull me up.
我准备好了  来吧
I'm ready. go.
-把手给我  -快点
-give it to me. -come on.
-再高点  -再使点劲儿
-be taller. -be stronger.
-用力拉  -快啊戴尔
-pull harder. -dale, come on.
拉  把我拉上去  快点  伙计
Pull. pull me. come on, man.
-我已经跳得够高了  -丹顿!
-I'm jumping as high as I can. -denton!
戴尔!
Dale!
我去找人帮忙  我去找人帮忙
I'll get help. I'll get help.
快跑吧  你这个小混蛋  我会找到你的
Go ahead and run, you little dipshit. I'll find you.
把灭火器给我
Give me that fire extinguisher.
好的
Okay.
就你和我  宝贝  把它放下  把袋子放下!
You and me, baby. drop it now! put the bag down!
现在!
Now!
妈的!
Fuck you!
去你妈的死警察!
Fuck the police!
杀了你个混蛋!
Motherfucking kill you!
-干吗要针对我?  -你又干吗要针对我?
-Why you doing this to me? -why you doing this to me?
该死!
Oh, shit!
别跑!
Come here!
我恨你!
I hate you!
不!  泰德  住手!
No! Ted, stop it!
过来啊  小杂种  来啊
Come on, bitch. come on
我非拧掉你的鸡巴不可
I'll twist your balls so tight.
这可是生死关头  宝贝
You're in the jungle now, baby.
天哪!
Jesus!
靠
Fuck.
真要命
Gonna die.
-你杀了  -我是迫不得已
-You killed -I didn't wanna do that.
因为你不会就此罢休
But you weren't gonna stop.
打死他!
Shoot him!
别激动  老兄
Just take it easy, buddy.
开枪啊  你个蠢货!
Shoot him, you dumb fuck!
我饿了
I'm hungry.
我要回家
I'm going home.
好吧
All right.
救我
Help.
我就知道你会心软
I knew you were going soft.
去见阎王爷吧  混蛋
Dinner's gonna be cold tonight, asshole.
操你妈  王八蛋
Fucked up, man.
-瞧你  福尔杰先生  -大哥
-well, look at here. mr. Folgers. -oh, man.
怎么样啊  先生?
What's up, sir?
-听着  大哥  我不是有意要打你  -闭上鸟嘴
-look, I didn't wanna hit you, man -shut the fuck up.
你以为你干掉我了吗  王八蛋?
You think you was gonna get me, motherfucker, huh?
把你那性感的小屁股坐稳了
You need to sit your little sexy ass down
等着去见上帝吧
and watch yourself get killed now.
好吧
All right.
这就是你要的结果吗?
You know what? this is how it's gonna be?
开枪吧  就此告终
All right. this is how it ends.
你刚被大宇蓝龙干掉了  混蛋
You just got killed by a daewoo lanos, motherfucker.
你能把我怎样?
How you like me now, huh?
真恶心
Gross.
瑞德?
Red?
索尔
Saul.
索尔  我来帮你了  哥们
Hey, saul. I came back for you, bro.
老兄  我会铭记在心的
I remembered, man.
为兄弟两肋插刀
Bro's before ho's.
-你骗了我  -是  我就骗了你
-you lied to me. -I did. I lied bigtime to you.
戴尔说你根本没得疱疹  可我还是相信你
Dale said that you didn't even have herpes and I said that you did.
坦白讲  从我们经历所有事起
Honestly, like, from now on, from everything that we've gone through
从看着这个混蛋被我的大宇撞烂开始
and, like, from seeing this asshole's nuts smashed with my daewoo
我就真心想当你的好朋友
i wanna be a better friend to you, like I really am.
他妈的爱死你了  爱死你
I fucking love you, dog. fucking love you.
我想成为你生命的一部分
I wanna be inside you, homes.
不再有谎言  瑞德
No more lies, red.
-这是我的时刻  -这是你的时刻
-this is my moment. -this is your moment.
瑞德!
Red!
我也不活了
You know what? I'm feeling it.
瑞德  我来了  宝贝
Red, I'm coming, baby.
你还真是蠢到家了
Your stupidity amazes me.
泰德!
Hey, Ted!
你杀了我哥哥
You killed my brother
屌你个白皮狗杂种!
caucasian son of cocksucker!
来吻我的蛋蛋吧!  要两次!
Suck my balls! two times!
去你的!
Bitch!
开枪吧
Bring it on.
该死  戴尔
Shit. Dale.
戴尔!
Dale!
见鬼了!
Holy shit!
抱歉  泰德
Sorry, Ted.
你被传召了
You've been served.
妈呀  妈呀  妈呀
Oh, shit. oh, shit. oh, shit.
索尔!
Saul! Saul!
醒醒  伙计!  这个地方要塌了!  快醒醒!
Wake up, man! this place is gonna collapse! come on!
快醒醒!
Come to me!
哥们  我不会让你死的
You're not dying today, friend.
我看顾着你呢
Not on my watch.
索尔  求你快醒醒
Saul. wake up, man, please.
索尔
Saul.
快醒醒
Wake up.
亲爱的索尔
Oh, sweet saul.
索尔
Saul.
醒了  醒了
Yes. yeah.
索尔  你没死
Saul, you made it.
-怎么了?  -没死
-what? -yeah.
我在哪里?
Where am i?
哥们  你没死
You made it, man.
-你救了我  -你又回到我身边了
-you saved me. -you came back for me.
谢谢
oh, thank you.
咋回事?
What happened?
见鬼
Holy shit.
那是什么?
What's that?
-瑞德?  -瑞德?
-Red? -Red?
瑞德
Red
瑞德  伙计  你从哪里冒出来的?
Red. where'd you come from, man?
从哪里冒出来的?
where'd he come from?
他回来救我们的
He came back to save us.
他救了我们?
He saved us?
好样的  哥们
All right, man.
我们都得救了
We all saved each other
我们都挺过来了  哥们
Oh, man. we made it, guys.
我们挺过来了
We made it. oh, we made it.
你好  你们正在收听的是公路之声
Hello, you're listening to pprpbp.
我是戴尔·丹顿
I am Dale Denton.
新的开始  渡过难关
New beginnings. getting over losses.
朋友  生命
Friends. life.
来接听第一个听众的电话
We have our first caller.
铃  铃  铃  好吗?
Yes, ring-ring-ring. how's it going?
我在线上吗?
Hi. Am I on the air?
是的  你是在戴尔的节目上
You are. you're about to get d'd by the dale.
D打头的那个人
A d in the face.
戴尔·丹顿
Dale Denton?
你是我的英雄
You're my hero.
你真的很棒  哥们
You are good, man. seriously.
-多谢  -为大众所熟识  真棒
-Thanks. -Gotta admit, you're pretty good.
-听起来很棒  -听起来像真的一样
-It sounds pretty good. -it sounds real.
-不错  -如果我闭上眼睛,那就像
-It's not bad, huh? -lf I close my eyes, it sounds like
-就像在广播中  -那就是广播  那是一个播音员
-You are on the radio. -that's the radio. that's a DJ.
-如果是你做广播  我会收听  -哥们  谢谢
-lf you were on it, I would listen to it. -thanks, man.
就像我奶奶一直在唱戏
It's like when my bubbe was always playing opera
我讨厌唱戏  但我奶奶喜欢
i hated it, but my bubbe loves it.
然后就习惯了  习惯成自然嘛
Then it grows on you. it grows on you. yeah.
就像瑞德  第一次见他就看他不顺眼
It's like Red. I didn't like Red when I first met him.
-你不喜欢我?  -你那么喜欢他
-you didn't like me? -you liked him so much
爱屋及乌嘛
i like you now.
我知道这听起来有点怪  但我们能做好朋友吗?
I know this sounds weird but can we be best friends?
就我们  说真的?
Just us, for real?
-我们都该做好朋友  -我们就该
-We should all be best friends. -we should.
你们俩都是我的好朋友
Seriously. you guys are, like, both of my best friends.
你之前不知道  现在知道了
You didn't know it. now you know it
我们都是好朋友
we'll all be best friends.
你知道那些被伤透心的"好朋友"?
you Know those hearts that break up, "best friends"?
我们该成为三个火枪手
We should get a three-way one.
-我不知道他们弄出来的  -我们要做第一
-I don't know if they make those. -we should make the first one.
我要当中间的  这样两边得好处
I want the middle piece, so it'll be crooked on both sides.
我就算道歉一千次都没法弥补
I know we've gone over this, but, like, 1000 pardons, 1000 pardons
求你们了
Please.
-我操  -哥们  我挺你  抱歉
-I fucked up -I was a dick to you, man. I'm sorry.
我知道我是个混蛋  我希望能弥补
I know I was an asshole. I hope I redeemed myself.
-我知道你跟我有交易  -有几次吧
-I know me and you had our deal. -we've had some times.
我感觉这里有事正要发生  是勃起了吗
I feel like something's happening here. is that a boner?
是公寓吗?  我们要同居了吗?
Is that a condo? that us moving into an apartment together?
我们要共度时光?
Is that us getting a time-share?
-你用烟灰缸砸他脸  -你打到我了  伙计
-you threw an ashtray at his face. -you hit me, man.
但还蛮有趣的
But it was kind of funny.
老兄  你用吸尘器打我
You hit me with a dustbuster, man.
我不是有意要伤你  就像"你最好别离开这里"
I didn't wanna hurt you. it was like, "you better not leave here."
-不打不相识  -就是
-that was such a good fight, man. -that was.
你弱智啊
You fuckhead.
-飞车感觉太棒了  -你们还经历了飞车?
-the car chase was awesome. -you got into a car chase?
-说笑呢吧?  天哪  -那
-are you kidding me? oh, my god. -yeah, it was
我的脚还穿透了挡风玻璃
I, like, had my foot through the window.
我的鼠蹊感觉像赛车叉骨
My groin I mean, I felt like a wishbone.
我现在眼冒金星
I'm trying to decide how stoned I am
像是濒临死亡一样
and just how on the verge of death am I now.
因为我血都快流光了
Am I seeing shit because I'm stoned or because I have no blood left?
-貌似你被打了7枪  -你得多吃点
-you've been shot, like, seven times. -you gotta eat.
-多补充点营养  -给
-you're losing stuff. -here.
-吃吧  -嗯  好的
-here. -yeah, okay.
-真是少有啊  -看  像个小孩子
-here comes the airplane. -look, like a baby.
真是个奇迹  我们都该花点时间
It's a miracle. I think we should all take a moment
想想发生在自己身上的奇迹
and think about what a miracle it is that we got out.
还有我们怎样变成为朋友
And that we became friends in the process
学习有关生活还有一些乱七八糟的东西
and learned some shit about life and stuff.
祈祷时我们可以互相握住对方的手
Should we touch each other's hands while we do it? okay.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
我们非常爱你们
I love you dudes so much.
有生之年我会记住这时刻的
I'll remember that for the rest of my life.
-瑞德?  -瑞德?
-Red? -Red?
瑞德  你还活着吗?
Yo, Red, man. you alive?
怎么了?
What's up, pal?
我是早上9点就睡的怪胎
I'm like the nerd at the sleepover who fell asleep at 9.
没关系  我们不会把弟弟塞你嘴里的
That's okay. we won't put our dicks in your mouth.
-天哪  -我奶奶到了
-oh, god. -hey, there's bubbe.
快走吧  快出去
Come on. let's get out of here.
我们该去看医生
Yeah, maybe we should go to the doctor.
她会载我去医院吗?
Do you think she'll drive me to the hospital?
我也是  我得去看看耳朵
Me too. I should get the ear looked at.
我耳朵该得到专业治疗
My ear should probably get professional attention.
-太糟了  -撑死我了
-it is bad. -that's a bullet burp.
我要么快死了  要么就去上大号
Either I'm getting ready to die or I'm gonna take a massive shit.
如果有人能带我去医院的话
If somebody could get me to the hospital.
血刚从我耳朵
Blood from my ear just
你们身上好臭
You guys smell like shit.
你死定了
You are in serious danger.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视修正制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多字幕 影视 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net